Note: The Tag-line 'Love Spin' Will Be Used In Movie Instead.
English Translation:
A Cricket Ball Bowled As If To Break One Way That Actually Breaks In The Opposite Way
नयायम्! शनैः...
वेगेन!
स अन्ताराष्ट्रियव्यापारी शरतमहोदयः किल?
किमर्थं दुष्टैः ताडितः?
न जाने.
भवत्याः तेन कः सम्बन्धः?
सम्बन्धस्तु...अहं...तस्य...मित्र...
अवगतं...विस्मरतु, महोदये.
रविजोश्यस्मि, वर्ताहरः.
चिन्ता मास्तु, महोदये.
सः क्षेमो भविष्यत्येव.
सः सुरक्षितः.
यदि भवान् समग्समये नागतं,
बहुकष्टम् भवेत्.
धन्यवादम्, महद् सहाय्यम् कृतम्.
- कापि समस्या नास्ति, महोदये.
विलम्बम् भवति,
मयेयं वार्ता प्रसारितव्या.
गच्छामि.
प्रसादवैद्य, इदानीन्तन प्रवेशितः पुरुषः साधारणो नैव
सः अन्तर्राष्ट्रीये प्रसिद्धः व्यापारी शरतः अस्ति.
यदि विषयमिमम् वार्ताहराः ज्ञास्यन्ते,
यावद्देशेनापि ज्ञातो भविष्यति.
तथा सः सावधानम् चेतितव्यः.
(तथा तस्य चिकित्सा सावधानम् कर्तव्या)
यदि वयं सावधानतया उत्तमतया चेतन्ति(चिकित्सां कुर्वन्ति)
सम्यक् प्रचारः भविष्यति तथा ख्यातेरुत्थानं भविष्यति.
वैद्यमहोदय, शरतमहोदयस्य रक्तप्रकारः कुत्रापि न लभ्यते.
हे भगवन्!
तथा मङ्गलूरे प्रत्येकस्य रक्तकोषस्य सम्पर्कः कर्तव्यः, अवगतम्?
आगच्छन्तु, रोगीनं प्रति. शीघ्रमेव.
वैद्यमहोदय, शरतस्य रक्तप्रकारः मिलितः.
- एवं वा? धन्योस्मि
कः दाता?
भगवन्, अनाथेव कदाप्यनुभूतवती.
वैद्या भवितुं मम बाल्यस्वप्नं वर्षानन्तरम् पूरयति
देशसेवायाः ममाशामपि.
मम कलाशालतः भारतवित्तावस्थावेदिकायां प्रतिनिधिरिव चिताहम्.
भागं भजितुं बैङ्गलूरं प्रति गच्छामि.
स्वीकरोतु,महोदये.
भगवन्, प्रयत्नेऽस्मिन साफल्यं भूयात् तवानुग्रहेण.
नवीनस्थानम्, नवीनजना!
कथं भवेयुः?
कुत्र हस्ताक्षरम्?
नमस्कारम्!
वेदिकायाः स्वागतम्.
- धन्यवादम्.
कुत आगता?
- मैसूरुतः
स्वात्यस्मि
- क्षणं तिष्ठ.
महोदये, सर्वाः सुविधाः सज्जीकृताः.
वेदिका श्व आरभते.
अवगतम्?
अद्य तूत्तमविद्यार्थिनां कृते पुरुस्कारवितरणं भवति.
प्रेक्षणं शक्यते.
सभागारं कुत्र??
- ऋजूया गच्छतु तदा दक्षिणम्
मम निमन्त्रणम्
पुनः मिलामः
- धन्यवादम्
प्रियाः विद्यार्थिनः
कृप्या तूष्णीम्
क्षम्यताम्, उपविशामि वा?
- आम! अवश्यम्
धन्यवादम्.
कृपया ध्यानम्
अद्य त्वस्मदीयो वार्षिकोत्सवः.
(उत्तमविद्यार्थिनां कृते पुरुस्कारवितरणम् कर्तुं) विद्यामन्त्री क्रिष्णप्पमहोदय आगतः
(उत्तमविद्यार्थिभ्यः पुरस्कारान् वितर्तुं) विद्यामन्त्री क्रिष्णप्पमहोदय आगतः
करतालेन स्वागतीकुर्वन्तु
अभिनन्दाः महोदय
एवम्
तृतीयस्थाने सहाना
अभिनन्दनम् सहाने
बहुसमीचीनम्
सम्यक्! सुकृतम्!
द्वितीयस्थाने रामः.
अभिनन्दनम् राम.
धन्यवादम्.
प्रथमस्थाने तु
एकः निमेषः, महोदय!
अहमपि गच्छामि, महोदय!
प्रथमस्थाने...
शरतः
प्रथमस्थानप्रप्ताय करतालं न दीयते वा?
भवन्तः किमर्थं नीरवम् उपविशन्ति
Sir, the student is little mental!
महोदय, सः चात्रः किञ्चित् उन्मादः
- उन्मादः?
इदृशाः चात्राः कलाशालातः बहिष्कर्तव्याः
सः उन्मादः इव प्रवर्तते किन्तु बहुप्रतिभाशाली एव
महोदय, पूर्वमुख्याध्यापकद्वयने तं बहिष्कर्तुम् प्रयत्नं कृतम् किन्तु तौ विफलौ जातौ
उभयाभ्याम् अकालसेवानिवर्तनं स्वीकृतम्
तस्मादेव अहं किमपि न कर्तुं शक्नोमि
महोदय, तेन तु शतम् छात्राणां समस्तप्रतिभा लब्धा.
बहुकुशलः शठः.
एवं वा?
सः उन्मादः प्रतिभाशाली कुशलः चात्रः कः एव?
प्राचार्यमहोदय, यथोक्तं सः तु सत्यम् उन्मादः.
समारोहम् एतादृशम् आगतः?
मुखमपि न दृश्यते.
मन्त्रिमहोदय, सः न
सः न?
कः सः महानुभावः?
♪ Rocking Star ♪
प्राचार्यमहोदय, सः आरक्षकाधिकारी वा?
I came to know just now that
he's a police officer, sir.
इदानीमेव ज्ञातं यत् सः आरक्षकाधिकारी, महोदय.
♪ Rocking Star ♪
Keeping it here is common style.
अत्र स्थापयामि तु साधारणा रीतिः.
Keeping it here is Sallu style.
अत्र स्थापयामि तु सल्मानस्य रीतिः.
अन्या रीतिः आवश्यकी किल?
♪ Rocking Star ♪
मम प्राचार्यमहोदयेन मद्विषये बहु भणितं किल?
That I'm mental, loose and crack.
अहम् उन्मादः, वातुलः, कितवः चेति
- आम्.
He would've told another thing also.
अन्यदपि भणितम् किल?
अहम् प्रतिभाशाली कुशलः इति.
ब्रह्मदेवः मन्दं मन्दम् हि मां निर्मितवान्.
I hate girls.
कनीः द्वेष्मि.
- किम्?
किन्तु कनीपीडकान् अधिकम् द्वेष्मि
तदर्थं तं ताडितवान्.
भो जनक!
- वदतु, पुत्र?
मास्तु. अधुना कृपया पुरस्कारं स्वीकरोतु
तथैव. स्वीकरोतु. ददातु.
समाप्तम्.
- By the way,
अहम् चिन्तयामि यत् भवता प्रथमस्थानम् तु लब्धं किन्तु भवते करतालम् न दीयते
यद्यपि अहम् रङ्गं प्रविशामि तर्हि करतालम् दीयते
एवं वा?
- आम्
करतालम्!
Claps for which you shell out money.
धनं दत्त्वापि करतालम् लभ्यते
Claps by the people who are
sitting here uninterested.
अत्र उपविशद्भिः निरुत्सुकैः करतालम्.
आवश्यकं न.
Without any selfish motive,
without knowing our background,
विना स्वार्थम्, विना परिचयम्
केवलं प्रतिभायाः कृते करतालम् यत् उच्चैः विनदति तदेव सत्यं करतालम्
तत् करतालम् मया श्रूयते!
♪ Rocking Star ♪
धन्यवादः.
When did you join police?
अये, कदा त्वम् आरक्षकसेवाम् प्रविष्टवान्?
- अहम्? आरक्षकसेवायाम्?
केनोक्तम्?
- किमर्थं वदितव्यम्?
आरक्षकसेवावस्त्रं धारयति किल?
इदं तु मम मातुः कृते
♪ Men are like water ♪
♪ They mix easily ♪
♪ Women are like milk ♪
♪ You touch and it gets spoiled ♪
♪ Listen, I'll tell you a super truth ♪
♪ Love is disaster to this world ♪
♪ Lord Brahma is very brilliant ♪
♪ He made a fantastic blue print ♪
♪ I'm electric ♪
♪ That's my only complaint ♪
♪ I don't use Axe body spray
but still girls follow me ♪
♪ I don't wear branded jeans but
still girls say 'I love you' to me ♪
♪ What should I do, Abdullah ♪
Full confuse, brother
♪ Men are like wind ♪
♪ They spread fragrance of flowers ♪
♪ Women are like snakes ♪
♪ If you touch, they bite you ♪
♪ Give up the old brand of 90's ♪
♪ Let the sound of pipes hit the sky ♪
♪ The snake will dance to the tune ♪
What did you say now?
♪ Love is sweet chocolate ♪
♪ Sometimes it is spicy cutlet ♪
♪ I've a fixed slate ♪
♪ I'll never take that route ♪
♪ I have doubt if I'm really that handsome ♪
♪ My mother keeps a dot
to ward of evil eye cast on me ♪
♪ She tells ♪
- My son is very cute!
♪ Men are like fire ♪
♪ Touch and you get burnt ♪
♪ Women are ♪
- Warn you to keep quiet!
इयं कीद्रशा प्रतिक्रिया?
Why are you so happy?
किमर्थं एतावत् उल्लासः?
Food in your hostel is really good.
तव आवासे भोजनं बहु स्वादिष्टमेव.
Just like the food in my orphanage.
मम अनाथाश्रमे इव
Wow! Good
बहुसमीचिनम्!
कस्माद्चित् कालात् प्रष्टुमैच्छम् यत्
who is this Sharath ?
कः शरतः?
Why entire college hate him?
कलाशालायां सर्वैः किमर्थं द्विष्टः?
Madhu Stop there!
मधो! तिष्ठ!
What happened? किं जातम्?
You've come to this college
today only.
अद्यैव कलाशाला आगम्यते?
Do you need to know about
that mental case?
तस्य उन्मादस्य विषयं ज्ञातुमावश्यकं वा?
Nothing like that
I found him interesting.
केवलं रोचकः इति मन्ये.
He's not interesting character
but irritating character.
रोचकः न सः क्षोभकः.
He hates love and girls.
सः प्रेम कन्यः द्वेष्टि.
But he beat a man for teasing
a girl, right?
किन्तु कनीपीडकम् ताडितवान् किल?
Yes.
आम्!
- Why is it so?
- किमर्थम्?
Had I known so much about him,
यदि तावत् ज्ञातम्
I would be the senior most
patient in mental hospital.
मनोरुग्णालये वरिष्ठरोगिनी अभविष्यमेव
Why?
किमर्थम्?
One of my friend Sheetal, was very
beautiful, went to propose to him.
मम एकं मित्रम् अस्ति, शीतला. सा बहुसुन्दरा. तया प्रेमनिवेदनं कृतम्.
Sharath
शरत?
- Yes
- किम्?
I love you
त्वयि स्निह्यामि!
- Oh!
- एवं वा!
Can't hear if there is an ear bud in ear.
यदि श्रवणयन्त्रं कर्णयोः धारयामि कथं श्रूयते
What did you tell now?
किम् उक्तम्?
Repeat.
पुनर्वद!
So many boys are after me.
कतिपयाः लाडिकाः मां कामयन्ति
But nobody has made me go
mad as much as you have.
किन्तु त्वम् इव कोऽपि न मामुन्मादं कृतम्
Please accept my sincere love.
कृपया मम निजं प्रेमनिवेदनं स्वीकुरु.
I love you
त्वयि स्निह्यामि
Am I your 10th victim?
तव दशमाखेटः अस्मि किल?
I've seen 4 boys who were
with you go to the saloon,
त्वया सह लाडिकचतुष्कम् शुण्डाम् प्रति गच्छमानम् दृष्टम्
three others went down the lane,
अन्यत् त्रयं विथ्याम् अग्रे गतवत्
news channels tell about others
vanishing from the world.
अन्ये तु जगतः अदृश्यं अभवत् इति दूरदर्शनेन भणितम्
What are you planning to do with me?
माम् किम् कर्तुम् कल्पितम्?
- Nothing like that.
- न किमपि एव.
I'm in love with you very seriously.
त्वयि स्निह्यामि तीव्रमेव
They were waste candidates.
ते तु मूर्खाः एव.
Okay, leave it.
साधु, मास्तु
Once candle wax melts,
wick is indeed useless.
द्रवीकरणतः परम् शलाका तु व्यर्थैव
This is latest fashion of girls.
कन्यानाम् अद्यतना रीतिः एव
Fashion of girls is tension for boys, it then
leads to emotion and ultimately to rat poison.
कन्यानाम् रीतिः तु लडिकानाम् आततिः, ततः परम् भावे परिवर्तते अन्ततः तु मूषकविषे
Do I need this?
आवश्यकम् वा?
Sharath
शरत
You girls ask for big money in
their wallets too along with lover.
कन्यः तु प्रेमिणा सह बृहत्कधनस्यूतम् वाञ्छन्ति
You loved 9 boys before me, did you ever
buy even a ₹ 0.50 chocolate for them?
इतः पूर्वम् नव लाडिकेषु स्निह्यति स्म, कदापि तेभ्यः पञ्चाशत्पैसमूल्यम् चाकलेहम् अपि क्रीतवती वा?
You know what, I didn't have ₹ 0.50 change.
ज्ञातं वा मम पञ्चाशत्पैसाः न अस्ति
Great!
बहुसमीचिनम्!
- I never asked them anything.
कदापि किमपि वस्तु न प्रार्थितम्.
They bought gifts for me
on their own will.
ते तु स्वेच्छया सर्वान् उपहारान् दत्तवन्तः
I accepted it to keep them happy.
तान् सुखयितुं सर्वे उपहाराः स्वीकृताः
That's all!
तदर्थमेव!
Why are you asking about past?
गतकालस्य विषयं कथं पृच्छसि?
Leave it, Sharath.
मास्तु, शरत
What do you want, dear?
किम् इच्छसि, प्रिये?
Should I jump down from this
roof or will you push me down?
अत्रतः मम कूर्दनम् अथवा तव नोदः?
Are you joking, Sharath?
शरत, परिहासम् करोषि वा?
Ever since you girls gave
the arrow of love to boys,
यदा युष्माभिः कनीभिः कामबाणम् मुञ्चन्ति स्म
we poor men do look like
jokers to you, right?
तत्समयतः वयं दरिद्राः लाडिकाः परिहासकाः इव दृश्यन्ते किल?
एवं वा? न जाने?
इष्टिकया आत्मानं ताडितवान्?
तव प्रेम धिक् अस्तु! त्वं धिक्!
तादृशः किमर्थम् वर्तते?
- कः जानाति एव?
तस्य विषये यदि बहु चिन्तसि चेत् तव पक्वकेशः भवति,
अथ वरान्वेषणं कष्टं भवति।
नूनं शयनं कुरु।
शुभरात्रिः
रोचते सः?
शुभारात्रिः।
406! घृतं नय।
406?
त्वम् अधिकारी वा?
अहं पुररक्षः?
आरक्ष्याधिकारी भवेः इति वदसि किल?
निजः अधिकारी भवेः इति उक्तम्
भाटकवस्त्रं धारयित्वा समाजेन निन्द्यस्व इति न उक्तम्
एकदिनं यावदेव आरक्षिवस्त्रं धारयामि चेत् इयत् तर्जसि,
यदि यावद्जीवितम् धारयामि मम अन्तं भवेदेव।
सप्ताहपर्यन्तं धारयामि। यावत् आवश्यकं तावत् पश्य। तदनन्तरम् प्रतिदीयताम्।
घृतं परिवेषय। चोराः गृह्यन्ताम्।
Nothing short in this act.
I tried a lot to keep you away
from following your dad.
I failed.
That's okay, where is dad?
He'll be on TV, watch it.
It was same in Lord Ram's marriage too.
Why I'm telling you this is because
bad time is looming large on you.
To avoid this every Saturday...
Daddy is after Saturn today.
What else your dad has to do?
He worried about future
of everyone except you.
You're like this and
he's like that.
I'm fed up with you both.
I'm also fed up with
this Bangalore traffic.
Astrology scholar is here only!
What about that?
That's pre-recorded.
To hell with it.
Why are you wearing police dress?
- That is for my mother.
Look Sharath, don't listen
to your mother,
Why I'm telling you is
It's true I loved your mother.
It wasn't compulsory to
marry the girl you love.
But listening to my mother,
I married your mother.
The moment I married her
and my future vanished.
I'm foretelling the future
of this world.
A love marriage here too!
Your future turned bright
after I married you.
I was just joking, Kausalya.
Forget about our future.
I've studied your son's future.
It's very bright.
He'll do so much that this
world will celebrate him.
I'll ask you a question, dad.
Think and answer me correctly.
I topped the college, would my principal
select me for Indian Economic Forum?
I must do.
I must do it.
He's college topper.
Principal says we must select him.
Forget about him, Forum is happening
in our college campus.
Internationally reputed corporate
companies are coming here.
Arrange everything perfectly.
Got it?
Don't forget it.
Hello vice-principal!
1 minute. You can go now.
- OK, sir.
It seems you wanted to meet me, sir.
Why don't you respect me
with people around?
You respect me when nobody is around.
I can't understand your character.
- I'm like that...different.
What's the use if I'm like everyone else?
Everyone must fear me, sir.
Fearsome are more powerful.
What do you say?
Okay, forgive me.
I've selected you to represent
at Indian Economic Forum.
Take this letter.
Thank you
One minute.
You're very brilliant.
My bad luck Forum is being
organized in our college.
Students from other colleges
would be here.
People of International reputed
companies would be here.
I consider this as your legs.
I beg you,
please don't attend the Forum.
Please save our college honor.
Anyhow you've selected me, right?
I can't avoid because
you're the college topper.
If not it'll dishonor
our college.
That's why, please do something
and withdraw yourself.
Save out college honor.
You say no need of murder,
commit suicide.
Don't worry sir,
the flag of our college honor
Flag of honor?
I love to dishonor it more
than honor, so I'll go.
What?
- Go that side.
My dear students, welcome to
The Forum of Indian Economy
Purpose of this forum is to find ways and means of using
new ideas and new techniques for the development of India.
There are 3 rounds in this program.
Big M N C's are waiting for good plans.
Your project could be anything,
Medical, Commerce, Engineering
Any degree
but it must help our country
to develop economically.
Now 1st candidate
Tejas
Good mourning everyone
I'm Tejaswi
[Hubli:
Coordinates: 15°21'42"N 75°05'06"E
State: Karnataka
Official language: Kannada]
And I'm here to explain about
my project plan. I'm from Hubli.
[Hubli:
Coordinates: 15°21'42"N 75°05'06"E
State: Karnataka
Official language: Kannada]
And this is most complicated project
what I'm going to exhibit in front of you.
[Hubli:
Coordinates: 15°21'42"N 75°05'06"E
State: Karnataka
Official language: Kannada]
This plan is regarding
the industrialization of India
which requests crores of money for the betterment of
infrastructure of our industries which we can't afford.
Thank you very much
Hi, I'm Madhu from Global College
Today I'm here in front of you
Hi, I'm Sandeep and now I'm here to say about
my project which is a banking system.
As you all know, today is having one of the best
Our next candidate
Mr. Sharath
Mr. Sharath from Global College
Hey look, he's sleeping
- Quiet
What bothers you? Keep quiet.
Mr. Sharath, we'll call your
name for the last 3 times.
Or else your name
will be eliminated.
No need, let him sleep.
It's necessary for him.
What are you saying?
Will you go or shall I go?
No need, let him sleep.
It's necessary for him.
What are you saying?
Will you go or shall I go?
No, you don't need to wake him up.
- If you don't, I'll do it.
I said no.
- I'm going.
Swathi
Sharath
- Mr. Sharath
This is the last call for you.
Or else you'll be eliminated
- Sharath
Sharath
Present sir.
Oh god!
- Crazy guy
I had millet balls early morning,
so I slept.
What should I do now?
- Tell about your project.
Okay.
My name is Sharath.
I'm a Commerce student .
Many from this stage talked about
businesses with crores of investment,
but nobody could guide how to get
those crore for the investment,
that's why I slept.
I'll not take much of your time,
I'll come straight to the matter ,
it's very easy to get money for
investment in our country.
How is that?
[Actual Answer: Approximately 1.22 billion (As of 2014) ]
What's our nation's population?
- 120 crores?
That's the only one thing we exceed!
If we get each one of them
to invest ₹ 1,
we'll get ₹ 120 crores, do we need
anything more than this investment?
Interesting,
How to do it?
Select me for the next round,
I'll answer you then.
Very clever
What a plan! Super
- Yes..yes...
OK. Fans must maintain restrain.
Excellent!
- Him and his plan?
Only you must appreciate him.
Thank you.
- Nice
That's a very good project, Mr. Sharath
Last but not least candidate
Miss Swathi
All the best
- Thank you
Hi, I'm Swathi.
I'm a Medical student
As Sharath said our nation is
highly populated,
we must use it as man power.
This means improving the health
of our people very important.
In order to do that, we have to make sure that every
facility is available at every part of our country.
So that any person, rich or poor,
is able to get that facility
Thank you
OK. Thank you all very much.
Results will be on boards and
through SMS's to your mobiles.
Thank you all once again.
You all can leave now.
Why did you wake up that mental man?
If you didn't, he would've got
eliminated from the Forum.
No, not like that, we knew about his
idea only after waking him up, right?
I think he's pretty brilliant.
How simply he told his idea!
If I hadn't, we would've missed
a good plan.
You waked him up,
did he at least thank you for that?
No! But mostly he would be
thinking about my help, right?
Sharath
Wake up
Dad!
- What's it, Sharath?
Yours was a love marriage, right?.
Indeed love marriage
but she has forgotten it.
Why are you raking up old memories?
Should I tell you about my love story
at this unearthly hour?
No dad, when you first saw mother,
[Mohini: The only female avatar of the Hindu god Vishnu]
did she appear everywhere
and in everything you saw like Mohini?
Indeed Mohini!
She was then and now too!
I know I can see her
even after I die.
That's why they're called Mohini.
- I too feel like that.
You?
Mohini?
Who is she?
Nobody!
Go daddy!
- Okay.
Go?
He's doing something!
I must tie Lord Anjaneya's
amulet to him. Go?
First time, something is happening.
I've insomnia.
Don't know why!
She woke me up, right?
Go to hell!
I must thank her tomorrow.
I must talk to him tomorrow.
How do I call girls?
I don't have any knowledge about girls!
Is it necessary to search
for a girl to say thanks?
Idea cancel
- Hi
Hi
Thanks
- Why?
While I was asleep,
for waking me up like bed bug.
Like bed bug?
What a comparison
Sorry
What should I say to him?
I'm Swati
Medical student
Greetings.
- Greetings!
Sharath
- I know
Shall we have a coffee?
- No need
No?
OK
Coffee heats up body.
Shall we have sugar cane juice?
Sure
Do you know sugar cane juice
has more heat than coffee?
Is it?
Leave it, youth must always be hot.
Tell me!
- What?
About you.
- Why?
Ever since I came here I've been
watching you till you spoke yesterday.
I found you different, special
and interesting.
I'm curious to know about you.
Which college are you from?
Mysore Medical College
Why?
You stay in Mysore about
140 km away from Bangalore,
but you're realized I'm an
interesting character,
but nobody in my college right from
principal to peon don't know this.
Look madam, can I call you as doctor?
Yes. OK
Look doctor, if you're the only one
who finds me interesting,
then I'm sure you too would be
quite an interesting personality.
Thanks
Would you like to have another
glass of sugar cane juice?
No...no...enough.
How much, brother?
- ₹ 20, brother.
It's ₹ 20, pay him.
Party is yours, right?
Had we gone to Coffee Day,
you would've spend ₹ 300.
See how this is over with just ₹ 20.
- Thanks
Sharath
Why do you hate girls and love?
Who said that?
- I got the news.
It's all rumors spread
by my enemies.
I hate girls.
But I like love.
Why is it so?
There are no good girls to fall in love,
girls are mad after love
but is it sincere?
There are no good girls to fall in love,
girls are mad after love
but is it sincere?
Powerful youth has gone waste going
for this magical word love.
I'll tell you a thing,
love is like an ice cream,
you look around and see, all you're
left with is just the stick.
Whether to keep it or throw,
if kept, where to keep it?
It's a lifelong confusion!
That's why I'll have only
cup ice cream.
Cup ice cream?
Hello...
- Come...come...
As love hits the young men,
first act will be on the
purse of the young men,
Whether love succeeds or fails,
it'll make hole to his purse.
If it is success hotel, films, dinner,
gift, mobile bills, petrol, etc.,
If it fails brandy, whiskey,
cigarette, marijuana, insecticide.
Whether love succeeds or fails,
only boys get ruined.
I think you're wrong.
Did you know Shah Jahan built
Taj Mahal for love?
I know it.
It isn't the mistake of Shah Jahan.
If any neighbor kingdom had
waged war with him,
forget about building Taj Mahal,
he wouldn't have time to think also.
True love has no value
in modern times.
[Frankincense: An aromatic gum resin (sticky substance) obtained from an African tree and burnt as incense]
Girls now are like frankincense,
they spread fragrance till we blow air,
[Frankincense: An aromatic gum resin (sticky substance) obtained from an African tree and burnt as incense]
the moment boys stop blowing air,
they throw boys like hot potatoes
and kill us.
We smoke but never smoke anyone.
Look, I think you've misconception.
All girls are not like that.
there are good girls too.
That's true.
Girls are of 2 types.
One is pure milk,
another is pure phenol.
Boys spend their lifetime
to find this difference.
But you are...pure milk.
You're not phenol like other girls.
Why?
When I asked, you paid happily
for the sugar cane juice.
Take it.
- No need.
Keep it.
- Why?
It's an insult to men if they
make women pay for a drink.
Didn't you fall in love
with anyone?
Love?
- Yes.
Me?
No chance.
Boys tell me that if you fall in love,
she appears in dreams and everywhere.
You mean?
- I mean...
Never any girl has appeared in
my dream or in my mirror.
Stop here.
I...
- Hey Sharath
What are doing here without
going to college?
Cigarette too!
I've brought an amulet from the
temple of Lord Anjaneya. Tie it.
Why?
You said some girl appeared in dream
and was waking you up.
That's why I got you this amulet
Tie it.
He's my creator.
She's Swathi.
- Sharath
Creator means?
- Father!
Greetings.
- Greetings.
Is she the girl who would carry
our family's future?
She's beautiful.
Dad, just go as you came.
I'll go son, auto is waiting, right?.
I've put up a lot to maintain,
don't bring it down, dad.
I beg you, dad, go home.
- I'll go but she's very nice.
She doesn't have the Mohini
features of your mom.
You go, dad.
Don't leave her,
hold tightly, be careful.
Swathi, please tell him to quit smoking.
He'll listen to you.
- Take him to home straight.
I'll go. You don't let me take
a good look at her.
Bye uncle
Why are you laughing?
That is...nothing.
Selected for next round.
- Congrats
Thank you
I'm also selected, look at this.
Is it?
- Won't you congratulate me?
I'm not in mood now. I'll congratulate
when we meet next time.
OK
If you ever come before me again,
don't push your hair like this, okay?
- Why?
I'm not in a mood to tell you that.
Why am I talking to you so much?
Am I a fool?
I'm not well.
- Hello...OK bye
I'm not in a mood to say bye also,
I'll say it next time when we meet.
If I stay here for few more minutes,
I feel I'll go mad.
Take it, son.
- Thank you
Tell me.
Tell me now, who was that girl?
- Girl?
Player Father!
Are you offering me a drink to make
me talk about that girl, right?
So be it.
Come on, tell me.
She's doctor bed bug,
she bites to wake up sleeping people.
That bed bug has bitten
specially my son.
Nothing like that, dad.
I've applied coconut oil,
I'll be fine.
What's fine?
You talked to that mental man
for so long.
I must get you checked up in
NIMHANS Hospital tomorrow morning.
Come on, Madhu
You've misunderstood him. He's very nice but
straight forward. It appears like madness to you.
You know I've never
talked to any boy so much.
But he's disturbing me in
a different way.
Hey! What are you saying?
Are you in love with him?
Are you mad?
- Yes, you are mad
My heart says you would get bitten
by that bug all your life.
Is it?
- It means you don't love him, right?
I feel so.
No need to feel,
I can see it on your face.
You've fallen for her.
You're madly in love with her.
I too was like you
when I saw your mother.
Daddy, so many have told
Love is waste over this drink.
Listen carefully
what I'm telling you now.
Those who couldn't keep their love
talk bad about love.
But how happy people are
who got true love!
Look at me!
You too are happy. You know why?
Because you're in love.
Go to your bedroom if not
I'll definitely beat you.
You're drunk, I'll go,
come carefully, son.
Don't fall.
Fall in love
Father!
Anyhow it's good you don't love him.
I'm feeling sleepy.
- Go to bed, I'll come.
Okay.
Am I in love with doctor bug
as my dad says?
If I knew her phone number,
I would've asked her.
He should've asked about
this confusion.
No...me...in love...me...no chance.
I haven't fallen for her.
So dear candidates
100 were selected for 1st round,
just 10 are selected for
the 2nd round.
It gets difficult from here.
The level of difficulty just increased.
And by the way,
We had announced award for the most
difficult and different project.
And that award goes to
Miss Swathi
Congratulations
- Congratulations Miss Swathi. Please come to stage.
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
- Congratulations
Swathi, Congratulations
I won
- I'm so happy.
Congratulations
- Thank you
Your presentation was very nice.
- Actually that was...
I'll be back in 5 minutes!
Hi
Bye
- What?
I wasn't in mood that day,
so I said bye now.
OK
Congrats
- Thanks
I wasn't in mood that day,
so I said now. Keep it.
I thought you'd get this award
but how I got...
How is it possible that
we both think alike?
I thought I would get but
some fools gave it to you.
Hey, no.
No smoking inside the campus, right?
- Yeah
No need of this.
- Actually
Had I been the judge,
I would've given the award to you.
I think you deserve it. So literally this
award must go to you. Take it, please.
No need.
- If you don't accept, I'll get upset.
No, you have to take it.
Take it, please.
I said no...
- Please accept it.
Swathi, what are you doing here?
Take your bag, let's go.
You carry on, I'll come later.
5 minutes.
Will you come or not?
Come fast.
- Sure
Stupid fellow
- Bye
Bye
Sorry
I pushed back my hair, it's my habit.
Leave it...
Will you please give your phone number?
Why?
Since we both got selected
for the 2nd round. So,
you know, to discuss about anything...
I can call you, right?
I'm Commerce student and
you're a Medical student,
Is there anything to discuss between us?
OK bye
- Bye
Hello, take down my number.
1 second
Tell me.
99 ...00 ...30 ...30...90
Send me a message.
- I will send.
What is there to discuss?
To ask about morning coffee,
breakfast or say good morning or night.
First time I'm giving my number
to a girl.
Me too! First time I'm taking
a boy's number.
Leave it, doctor. You're not like other girls.
No second thought about it.
Bye
See you
Jupiter in 12th place and
Moon in 9th place!
What else would result!
It's happening as I said!
Why are you laughing, son?
I'm crying, dad.
- Crying? Why?
I too got ruined like all other boys.
I've also fallen in love, dad!
My god! It's bad omen to cry
like this at midnight.
Be happy son to have fallen
in love like all others.
Is it?
- Then what?
My prediction has come true.
I told your mother that our son
would surely fall in love.
You've saved this family's honor.
The moment I saw the girl,
I calculated.
Every planet around was
in favorable place.
You got yourself a good girl.
You said the truth, dad.
Dad, she is not like other girls.
She doesn't change lovers
morning and evening.
She has asked for the
phone number from me only.
Then?
Poor girl sacrificed her award for me.
She has proved prize is sweet
and sacrifice is eternal.
What's your future plan?
I'll propose to him next.
Swathi, how could you
fall in love with him?
You know how genuine he is?
The man who never spoke to
a girl till now,
how cute he was with me!
He's so cute
I feel I'll be happy with him.
OK, next?
Next, I'll go propose my love to her.
If I propose to her now,
the touch-me-not name in college
would go to the dogs.
I feel like crying thinking
about it, father.
Shut up!
Love mustn't have any restrictions.
Love mustn't have ego.
There is no place for status in love.
One must become gentle like
football without air.
No use in telling you.
Her planetary position makes her
to propose first if you don't.
That's what you need in life.
If that happens,
in college I can boast
I didn't go after her,
she came after me,
and maintain my range as it is.
Dad, tell me she'll express her
love to me.
I'll tell him tomorrow.
I'll express my love to him.
No Swathi, look I warned you
not to love but you loved him.
It's OK
Please listen to me,
wait for few days,
it's better to make him
propose to you.
Because he's a strange man.
Let him commit himself to you.
Would he propose to me?
Look, if you propose and if he
rejects, you'd be in trouble.
Are you confident he would
express his love to you?
I do.
Then, forget it.
Okay?
OK
- Okay for me too.
She'll propose in few days, right?
I'll wait till then.
- That's good.
Lovers must be alone
when love sprouts.
Grief of separation is an experience.
What else can I tell you?
Fry in pan, pain in love,
if you get cheated, eat jail food.
If I like having jail food.
I love you, Swathi
- I love you, Sharath
♪ Something has happened to me ♪
♪ Without my knowledge ♪
♪ My heart has skipped a beat ♪
♪ I'm enchanted ♪
♪ My sweet heart ♪
♪ My life has taken a dramatic turn ♪
♪ I was like a sage ♪
♪ You are life of happiness ♪
♪ Adjusting your hair, you turned
my world upside down ♪
♪ Something has happened to me ♪
♪ Without my knowledge ♪
♪ I'm a vagabond ♪
♪ You're gentle ♪
♪ Love story has started ♪
♪ Forgotten the way to my home ♪
♪ Come, show me the way ♪
♪ I thank you ♪
♪ I wrote a paper ♪
♪ Give your hands the paper
to say what is in the heart ♪
♪ I'm scared ♪
♪ There's no one more beautiful than you ♪
♪ You're so attractive, my love ♪
Then?
♪ I'm enchanted ♪
♪ My sweet heart ♪
♪ My life has taken a dramatic turn ♪
♪ I was like a sage ♪
♪ You are life of happiness ♪
♪ Adjusting your hair, you turned
my world upside down ♪
♪ I have little doubt if it's really me ♪
♪ You've changed me ♪
♪ I was undefeated ♪
♪ Now I'm weak ♪
♪ When I see you laugh ♪
♪ Ego stops me from saying though I love you ♪
♪ Nobody has disturbed me as much as you ♪
♪ You can't find a better lover with heart
than me in this entire world ♪
Then?
♪ I'm enchanted ♪
♪ My sweet heart ♪
♪ My life has taken a dramatic turn ♪
♪ I was like a sage ♪
♪ You are life of happiness ♪
♪ Adjusting your hair, you turned
my world upside down ♪
♪ Something has happened to me ♪
♪ Without my knowledge ♪
So dear candidates
Only 5 have been selected
in 2nd stage.
And out of this, the best presentation
award goes to Mr. Sharath
Why is he shouting like that?
Good
Congrats
Congratulations
All the best
Didn't I tell you that he would
get the award, Madhu?
He's so intelligent.
You know what happened
Hello doctor!
Madhu, he's coming
I'll call you later.
Hi
- Actually
I thought they would give the award
to you in this round.
Is it?
- Your presentation was so good.
You presented it better than me.
No, its proved once again
that they're fools.
Had I been the judge,
I would give the award to you.
So the award belongs to you.
Take it.
You deserve the award more.
It's yours
Please take it.
I've never given up anything in life
for another person.
But there is justice in this.
You deserve it.
Then...
- Then?
Then...take it if not I'll get upset.
Sharath, hey
Thank you
Shall we have sugar cane juice?
I've cold.
- Cold?
Did you apply Vicks?
There is a tablet for it.
No, let's go to the doctor.
Sharath, I'm OK
I'm perfectly alright.
Why do you care so much about me?
That is...
- That is...
Please Sharath, say it!
- I mustn't get overwhelmed.
Not much care,
just said about doctor casually.
I don't care myself...
You held it perfectly, bro!
If she had got hurt...
Who this mad man is?
What if she is hurt?
What will you do now?
Where are you, boys?
He's the guy!
Where will you go now?
Hello, you were going overboard!
I still didn't do wrong,
if I do one...
All of you would die!
No...no...- I can't tolerate
a tear or speck in my lover's eyes.
Not just I don't let even
her father beat her.
How dare you hurt her right
before my eye!
Bloody!
- Sharath
I'll take your hand!
What are you doing here?
Go to the hospital.
You were bleeding, why were you watching
fight instead of going to hospital?
No...
- At least take medicines properly, doctor.
Have food on time.
- OK
I adjusted my hair!
No problem.
Leave it.
Why did you ask me not
to adjust my hair?
I can see all the qualities of
ruining my life in that hair.
How?
Not in mood now,
I'll tell next time.
Bye
- Sharath
You're a good man.
- Is it?
News to me, why?
Not in mood now,
I'll tell next time.
Bye
I can't hold on anymore,
I must tell him tomorrow.
I must say I love you, Sharath.
I can't hold on anymore.
Dad, I'll get ruined if I trust
your astrology.
I must tell her tomorrow.
When will tomorrow arrive?
Should I offer flower to her?
No! I'll propose in my style.
I got many ideas hearing you.
Let's meet and discuss again.
Meeting?
Don't worry! We'll sometimes meet up
But this place is new to me.
I can't meet alone.
OK, we'll meet up sometime and talk
- OK
OK. See you. Bye
- Bye
Hey boy! Come here.
Tell me.
You were talking to her so closely,
what were you talking about?
Why do you want to know?
- Right.
Why?
You know there's something
between us, right?
If you enter central and park with side stand, I feel
like someone is pricking my heart with a pin.
Try to understand me!
She was talking to me,
what bothers you?
After you said this,
you must maintain at least
100 meters away from her.
If I see you near her...get lost!
Stay distant if 2 people
are in love,
if you try to get between them...
Spoiled my mood!
Why Sharath hasn't come today also?
Shall I call him on phone?
Why should I call him?
Your Romeo has proved that he is mental.
Why? What happened?
Were you talking with Sandeep?
Yes, he was saying something
and I was listening to him.
Watching this he beat up Sandeep.
Not only that he has warned him too.
It seems he must stay at least
100 meters away from you.
Poor man! Sandeep himself told me this.
- Is it?
Yes, Swathi.
That's why I told you not to love him.
If he suspects you so much now,
I don't want to tell anything else.
Your wish.
I didn't get selected for the final,
you're intelligent
and you got selected.
Concentrate on your project,
you can think about this later.
No Madhu...
Go to your room,
I've to run an errand.
Why did Sharath behave like this?
Everyone going towards airport
isn't a flight passenger, right?
Isn't it wrong to think he was
flirting just for talking to her?
Anyway it was good to beat that idiot.
If he had any such intention,
he would give up now.
I'm not prepared for girls.
I must prepare now for the final round.
Swathi had met with an accident.
- What? Accident?
Swathi...accident patient.
- 1 sec.
1st floor, 3rd room
- Thank you
Please get up!
- Thanks
I thought you'd have lost limbs
in the accident.
But it was a very small accident.
Take rest, final round is near.
Yes...yes...
Sharath?!
Sharath, that is...
- What's wrong with you, Sharath?
What did I tell you?
Didn't I warn you to stay away from her?
Didn't I tell you?
Sharath please
Can't you understand
if I tell you once?
Do you've to stick on to her always?
Leave him, Sharath
- I'll kill you today!
Stop it, Sharath. What happened to you?
Did I get slapped by you?
That too for him!
What happened to me?
How was I?
You needed this!
Why did you beat him?
What was his mistake?
He was helping me to sit up.
You're behaving like a savage.
Aren't you ashamed?
Stop it.
Not me, you must be ashamed of it.
Because you're behaving
like a bitch.
I mistook you to be a good girl.
You too are like all other girls.
Touching him physically...
I...a girl like you...
I knew about girls
but still got cheated.
I came to tell you something.
Good, I didn't tell you.
You gave me something, right?
- Sharath
I must forget her totally.
What happened to you, Swathi?
Where are you going?
I'm going to native, Madhu.
I can't stay in a place
where he lives!
♪ Without you it's dark and
barren all the way ♪
♪ Without you life is nothing
but despair ♪
♪ Without you life has changed
it's course ♪
♪ Without you life has become single ♪
♪ Forgetting romance, approval
I'm living alone ♪
♪ Forgetting love, generosity,
♪ My loneliness is all mine ♪
♪ Everyday is an
independence day for me ♪
♪ Windstorm has left my life ♪
♪ You left me mid sea ♪
♪ No more at the mercy of fate ♪
♪ I've my heart,
what else do I need ♪
♪ New life is all mine ♪
♪ Forgetting romance, approval
I'm living alone ♪
♪ Forgetting love, generosity,
Young Global leader of
Indian origin Sharath,
has been chosen to represent India in
economic and business implementation forum.
Hi Swathi
How are you?
I'm fine.
I'm fine too.
I've good news for you.
- What?
I'm getting married
on 28th of next month.
Don't miss it, you must make it.
- Oh my god
Congratulations. I'll surely make it.
Of course I'll be there.
Thank you Swathi.
Why not forget him and
start new life?
I don't think about him,
I've forgotten him for 2 years now.
Hello
- Hello Sharath. How are you, son?
Fine
But...
- But?
Tell me, son.
What's the matter?
I made a grave mistake
in Swathi's matter.
I became selfish that she must talk
and move close with me only, dad.
Dad, I shouldn't have slapped her.
In a fit of rage I did it.
It was my mistake.
It was my mistake, right dad?
Let bygones be bygones,
forget everything and
come back to India.
Start a new life here.
I can't dad...
it was my first love, dad.
I'm unable to forget her, dad.
♪ The place where you fought with me,
memories of it are dominating me ♪
♪ The thorn you let in my heart ♪
♪ It is blooming now
to spread fragrance ♪
♪ Coming far away from you ♪
♪ Turning a new leaf in life ♪
♪ Forgetting romance, approval
I'm living alone ♪
♪ Forgetting love, generosity,
♪ Without you it's dark and
barren all the way ♪
♪ Without you life is nothing
but despair ♪
OK, I'll inform to boss. Excuse me, sir.
- Yeah
Sorry sir. The meeting you just fixed today
has been postponed to 17th of this month.
I mean the day
after tomorrow.
That's something...
Then today is 15th March
- Yes, sir.
Today is Swathi's birthday!
Shall I wish her?
Hello
Who is it?
- Sharath
Which Sharath?
Sharath
Tell me!
Happy Birthday, Swathi
- Thank you
How are you, doctor?
Fear of losing you...
jealousy...love...
It forced me to slap you.
I love you, Swathi.
I've been regretting every moment
after slapping you.
I really love you. I'm unable
to live without you, Swathi.
It was my mistake. Please try to understand
me. I just can't live without you.
Sharath, I never had any
such feelings for you.
I'm getting engaged.
Please don't ever call me again.
Thank you
OK
I love you, Sharath.
I don't want to lose you at any cost.
I love you
It seems somebody beat leading
industrialist Sharath in Mangalore.
Why are you selling
evening paper in early morning?
Murderous attack on
leading industrialist Sharath!
Who could've done it?
Leading industrialist Sharath has
been assaulted in Mangalore.
He went to Mangalore to attend
a friend's wedding...
Leading industrialist Sharath...
Leading industrialist and
global young leader Sharath,
was attacked and
assaulted by rowdies.
He was coming back from Mangalore
after attending a friend's marriage,
this murderous attack took place!
Reason for the
attack is unknown.
Look at this!
- Police are investigating.
Sharath has been admitted in
a prestigious medical hospital.
Press reporter Ravi Joshi has
succeeded in saving Sharath's life.
Ravi Joshi is talking to our reporter...
Can you please give us complete
details about this incident?
What happened madam?
I feel dizzy.
Come, take rest.
Don't worry about him.
Come...come...you're a doctor,
you must take care of yourself.
Sister, get glucose ready.
Slowly...
He may regain consciousness
anytime now, doctor.
Take care of him.
Murderous attack on industrialist Sharath.
While returning from Mangalore after
attending a friend's wedding.
this incident took place.
He was with his future wife Swathi...
Has Swathi agreed to marry me?
She donated blood to you, she was
awake all night to look after you.
She is taking rest now.
- Can I see her?
You can't in this condition, sir.
- I must see her!
You mustn't do like this.
I must see Swathi.
I'm fine, I must see Swathi.
Please don't strain yourself.
Don't strain yourself...slow...
She's fine.
Just rest will help her.
You go out.
You take rest.
You've strained yourself.
No sir, media people are
waiting outside.
Okay, sir.
We'll wait outside.
Come, let's go out.
I never had any such feelings for you.
I'm getting engaged.
Don't ever call me again.
Mother, I'm coming to India.
Leading industrialist Sharath
has come to India.
People are curious about
his sudden visit to India.
Are you here with any new plan, sir?
This is purely personal visit, that's it.
About other plans, not now,
I'll talk to you later.
Allow me to go home.
I'm home!
Wait a minute!
Over.
May God bless you long life!
He hasn't forgotten it yet.
Come quickly, mom.
- I will come.
What else, dad?
Is your BP and sugar under control?
Mom, don't serve oily food to dad.
Both of you take care of your health.
Both are aged, I'm saying.
Your dad's BP and sugar can't
get controlled with food.
Is it? Why, dad?
Has any new planet entered your life?
Planets are...
- Enough of joke, Sharath.
You got fame and fortune!
But what is the use?
You still think about Swathi and
we know the pain you're going through.
I don't like to see my son sad.
Please son, get married soon.
I'll find you a good girl.
Your dad had 2 mild heart attacks.
You keep quiet.
How long can we keep quiet
with pain in heart?
We've everything but no peace of mind.
Look Sharath. Though we're
seeing you after 2 years,
you still look like
college student to us,
but without our knowledge or yours,
you've changed a lot.
Change is circle of life!
Swathi too would've
changed like you.
So, forget her and
accept your mother's choice.
Everyone would be fine.
Father, I...
One more thing.
It isn't my intention that your mother
needs a daughter-in-law to look after her,
for your future, for your life,
it must have a meaning,
that's our only intention!
Please listen to your mother
and agree to marry.
He won't
listen to us.
I can understand
your worry.
But this is not an issue
to force him.
Okay mother!
I'll marry the girl you select.
Are you
happy now?
Watch out! We'll find the
most beautiful girl for you!
Thank God, he agreed.
Shall I take
leave, mom?
Take blessing, son.
May you be blessed with success.
Have a pleasant journey, son.
Call dad.
Cancel the flight,
I'll go by road.
No need, I'll go alone.
I've arranged it, sir.
I told you, right?
Mom, bye.
Dad! Shall I take leave?
- Have a safe journey!
Kind India, Bangalore!
It's been years since
I listened to it.
...has been honored
with doctorate degree.
Fans all over state are celebrating it.
Lorries and buses were off the road
protesting against the petrol hike.
Common people were affected by it.
Our govt....our people...great!
Leave me!
Please...please leave her...
- Go away!
Hey, start the car!
We'll taste Karnataka fish today!
Bloody idiots! Is it Assam?
Karnataka!
We don't spare if you touch
stone, earth or water!
If you dare touch a girl right before
our eyes, would we spare you?
Get him, don't leave him.
Leave...leave me...
People of Karnataka are famous
for ripping out nerves!
Find and gather yours and
leave the place.
Leave!
Thank you
very much, sir.
When you love a girl,
you're her body guard!
Along with loving a girl
like our Crazy star,
we must learn Karate
like Karate king!
All boys in love must learn Karate!
I think your lover is very lucky.
Go!
Thanks brother.
For saving his lover, he hit
my heart by bringing up my love.
I'll forget Swathi by the time
I come back mom Narayana's marriage.
Should the bus
break down now?
Standing in rain!
My damn fate!
Some car is coming,
please stop...stop...
Stop the car please.
Looks like God has sent a car,
Come...Come...
Please open the dickey, son.
She'll keep her luggage.
Shall I start, granny?
What's this, son? You stopped
the car promising to give lift.
Look, I've urgent work.
The man marrying my grand daughter
would be waiting for me.
Because I've the sacred thread with me.
I must take it to them.
Go fast, son!
You look quite familiar.
- Do I? Where?
Are you TV actor?
I used to...
but not now.
That's why I don't see
you now on TV.
Why are you driving it like a cart?
Go fast!
I've herbal medicine
to charge up!
Shall I give to make you drive
at jet speed?
No, please.
Where are you all going?
Not all but we 3 are
going to Haale Beluru.
She is going to Mangalore.
I'm also going to Mangalore.
I'll drop you in your place and go.
Goddess Belruamma, in this rain,
with buses on strike,
you've saved us, mother!
I'm grateful to you!
Are you going alone in this car?
What to do? I'm alone.
- Is it?
Marry as quickly as possible.
This car doesn't look good
with lone passenger.
It looks good if you go
as a couple.
My husband took me on bike
when we were married.
Do you know how happy I was then...
Granny... Rain has stopped but not your talk.
Please come quietly, granny.
You don't like me talking, leave it.
We've reached my place,
please stop the car.
Haale Beluru
Stop...stop...
- Yes.
Haale Beluru
Do you see the board?
That's the place.
Haale Beluru
Do you see the board?
That's the place.
Get down quickly.
You said she was going to Mangalore, granny.
Why did she got down?
Why did you get down?
You could've traveled
to Mangalore, right?
No need, granny.
I'll manage myself.
You're alone,
where will you do, dear?
He appears like a good boy.
I don't think he would rape you.
If by any chance he rape you,
marry him immediately.
If he refuse,
threaten to file case going to DD9.
Oh god!
He would marry you in fear.
Good boy.
You can't find such good boys.
No, granny...that is...
not like that...
Nothing to it, transport men are
on strike, useless buggers!
Come with me, listen to me.
- Granny, listen to me.
You listen to me.
You'll go to Mangalore safely.
I'll stand guarantee for it.
Bring it down!
What is it, granny?
- What?
Take her to Mangalore safely,
if you get any crazy ideas,
she knows Karate, be careful!
Go...go...
I don't think she will talk to me.
Let me ask her.
♪ You've come like
the light of my life ♪
the treasure of love ♪
Will you please
switch off the radio?
Let it play, song is matching
the situation.
Hearts of boys and
dog's tail are same,
though tied with a stick,
on seeing a girl, it turns crooked.
Just a while ago
I made a resolution.
To forget you completely.
My bad luck I found you.
You won't live long.
Again the same...
How are you, doctor?.
Fine.
How did your
engagement go?
Whose engagement?
Your engagement!
You said your
marriage is fixed.
I'll go to Mangalore on my own,
you carry on.
Hello...hello...doctor!
So, she's not engaged.
Is engagement canceled
or not engaged at all.
Hello doctor!
Your luggage!
Love Spin
Nothing happened yet.
Open the dickey.
You didn't tell me about
your engagement.
Open the dickey.
Has your engagement
got...?
I don't want
to talk about it.
I'll go to Mangalore on my own,
you carry on.
Love Spin
I can go but it's crime according to
boys' rules to leave girl midway.
Look, transport men are on strike.
You won't get bus.
I'm also going to Mangalore,
come with me.
Just because I'm going to Mangalore,
you don't have to go there only.
Mind your own business.
Don't behave silly.
I needed this.
Wait a minute.
Don't get intimate with new girl
and don't help a girl you know.
Look at this invitation, I'm going to Mangalore
to my friend's marriage.
Are you going to this marriage?
Did Madhu invite you?
How?
Madhu? Which Madhu?
I'm going to my friend
Narayana's marriage.
Narayana....Madhu...
I'm also going to the
same marriage.
Oh God!
What a divine play!
I wanted to forget
but you brought her before me.
You made her miss the bus
by creating transport strike.
You've made us both attend
the same marriage.
Seeing all this I think
we'll marry and have children. Isn't it?
Nothing, leave it.
Come, I'd do the same even if
granny was in your place.
I'll come.
But we both are strangers there.
Same dialogue.
I'm a master of 'Love Spin'!
A 'Love Spin' for me!
Swathi, understand me and
come into my life,
then, you can sit like queen and I'll be your
driver, and we can go on long drive non-stop.
♪ Love Spin, in the spin of Kumble ♪
♪ Love Spin, in my love ♪
♪ Love Spin, in her words ♪
♪ Love Spin, What am I to do ♪
♪ Love Spin, listen men ♪
♪ Love Spin, women tell ♪
♪ Love Spin, all of you tell ♪
♪ Love Spin, what am I to do ♪
♪ If you met your lover,
you need little courage ♪
♪ Oh God, my life has become
sinful without my knowledge ♪
♪ If you met your lover,
you need little courage ♪
♪ Oh God, my life has become
sinful without my knowledge ♪
♪ I'm unable to say a word ♪
♪ My meter is down ♪
♪ I can't believe it ♪
♪ I don't know why ♪
♪ Star has changed and
my BP has raised ♪
♪ I'm prone to get heart attacks now ♪
♪ She kills me with looks
now and then ♪
♪ She adjusts the hair
to open flashbacks ♪
♪ Love Spin, in the spin of Kumble ♪
♪ Love Spin, in my love ♪
♪ Love Spin, in her words ♪
♪ Love Spin, What am I to do ♪
♪ Marriage must get confirmed
by parents ♪
♪ I'll get you rose petal jam everyday ♪
♪ What a promise, my Romeo! ♪
♪ Heat up very cool rose petal jam ♪
♪ And eat jamun throughout life ♪
♪ What a promise, my Romeo! ♪
♪ Heat up very cool rose petal jam ♪
♪ And eat jamun throughout life ♪
♪ Our love is very sweet ♪
♪ May it not get affected
by any disease ♪
♪ Why do you worry
when I'm a doctor ♪
♪ Let's happily start family
as soon as possible ♪
♪ Let's forget the rules
of family planning ♪
♪ Let's build a new
Indian cricket team ♪
♪ Love Spin, in the spin of Kumble ♪
♪ Love Spin, in my love ♪
♪ Love Spin, in her words ♪
♪ Love Spin, What am I to do ♪
Come...come...come forward,
don't touch the car.
You come to ward off evil,
you come forward to take photos.
My friend has come mom abroad
for my marriage.
I told you not to disturb him, right?
Come, ward of evil eye cast on him.
Take video,
I've paid you well, right?
Do you know how happy I'm
because you've come?
I'm not the groom, it's you!
You too will get married soon.
Don't worry.
Do you say like that?
Let me see, come.
Freshen up in 5 minutes.
- Please give him way.
You go, he'll be here only,
you carry on. Come.
No need of this extra arrangement.
Let me be simple as usual.
I'm fortunate that you've come to
my marriage, thank you, friend.
Not you, I must thank you.
Looks like your marriage will
become a turning point in my life.
Turning point?
Come, I'll tell you.
- Come.
Did he propose again in car
and troubled you?
No, he called me on my birthday
and proposed to me,
but I avoided him by lying
that I'm getting engaged.
But I feel he has
changed a lot.
Why? What has happened
to you again?
What did he tell you?
What did he do with you?
Think about it again.
First I must take my husband
to task.
How did he befriend Sharath?
I'll take a special class
on our first night.
Come, friend.
If you eat food of my region,
you'll forget everything else.
Why are you going there?
- To eat.
That's not for you.
This special seat is for you.
Would anyone sit there to eat?
Keep quiet, buddy.
Friend, I arranged it specially for you.
- For God's sake, will you keep quiet?
Though you're famous,
you're still down to earth.
Okay, go.
I'll be back in a minute, friend.
Eat well, I'll not get
married again in life.
I'm very happy to sit with you
and have food.
Should there be a vacant
chair only next to him?
Full filmy style!
Why?
- For dropping me here.
I've done nothing,
it was an act of god.
How come you're
sitting next to me?
Chair was vacant,
so I sat.
My heart too is vacant for
the past 2 years.
I never desired to meet
but met you.
We're in a marriage house.
Under the canopy!
I can hear marriage band too distantly.
Banana leaves are
adorning the entrance.
Only bridal
dress is missing.
Isn't it?.
Love Spin
Time isn't good.
You're great batsman Sharath, right?
- Batsman?
Yes.
In a way I'm
a batsman.
I've seen you everyday on TV.
I and my daughter
see you.
My daughter loves
you so much.
Do you know that
she kiss you in TV?
Did you see me batting on TV?
I didn't play cricket
in recent past.
I've seen you play
on TV everyday.
That you're a
great batsman.
Aunt, that's businessman
not batsman.
Oh businessman?
I want a shot
with you.
I mean a photo!
- Photo?
I can't see a photographer here.
Where's he?
I'll take one.
- You're wanted here, Musthafa.
One minute,
I'll take one snap.
Is it my girl?
Done.
Is it you, Musthafa?
Take my snap
with him.
Come.
Please sit.
- I'll come now.
Please sit...hello...
One minute.
- I'll come back.
Who is she? Too much!
Have you gone so far?
I'll not spare him.
You're a famous man.
VIP too!
Though you're great, why are you hitting
hard on my stomach and my heart?
What did I do?
What did you do?
The lady with whom you took the snap,
she's my ex-lover.
Is it?
I bought her so many goodies
as young lover,
that I ran up ₹ 10,000 in debt
in those days,
unable to repay,
I ran away mom there,
I earned back money
and came back for her
she got married and
went away to her husband's home.
Then?
- Then what? After marriage had kids.
To her?
- No, me.
How come?
In the sorrow of losing lover,
I opened up many branches.
You say love, isn't it wrong
to do like this?
Wrong...isn't it wrong?
That's why I've come back for my love.
What about the
girl who married you?
She went in search
of her lover.
I came back after knowing my lover
has divorced her husband.
Yours is very long tale.
But I don't know how
I'm hurting you in this.
We were about to mix
like milk and honey,
if you come between us like lime juice,
milk will get spoilt, sir.
It will be obsolete.
Neither use it as milk
nor with honey.
Are you saying I'm in love
with that aunt?
Yes.
Only this was lacking
in my life.
What did you say
your name was?
Come here.
- I'll not agree for any adjustment.
Come closer. Look there!
The girl in pink sari.
That's my lover.
I love her.
Not that aunt.
Keep the aunt for yourself.
What a great
thing you've said, sir!
You've hit my heart, sir.
You're a photographer, right?
I'm world famous
in my town.
Come here.
Take good photos
of my girl.
I need it
when I'm alone.
I'll take good one.
Why?
If you don't take
good photos,
I'll definitely take your girl.
I may miss her second time,
I'll take her photos now.
Tell me.
Don't you remember the stick ice
I bought you?
Stick ice?
So many had bought it for me.
I don't remember.
I've come back to
buy you stick ice.
You mustn't eat if anyone else buys,
only I must buy it for you.
You've been bringing
it for 10 years.
Buy or make me eat,
do whatever you want to do.
I'll make you eat my stick ice,
first I'll take photos for my boss.
Where is she?
She's here.
I must take a photo without
her knowledge.
Miss! Now I'll click.
Missed again.
Please take my snap.
- Go that side.
- Go away.
You want photo with that lousy face,
go away.
Missed her again.
She's here.
It's better to take photos
with permission.
Bus strike, I faced so many problems.
If you give a good pose,
I'll take a good photo.
My photo? Why?
Your lover Sharath wanted
a good photograph of you.
Is Sharath your lover?
Just one photo, please.
If you don't give a pose,
he'll take away my lover.
Please, one photo.
Where is Sharath now?
Where's she?
Why are you sporting a beard?
What to do? Unemployed.
- Is it?
Did you try with people I referred?
He got beaten up unjustly
in Swathi matter.
I must say sorry to him.
Oh no! Why did he
come here?
Yes, mom.
I've got photos of beautiful girls.
I've selected 3 among them.
I'm sure you'll like them.
Mother, I don't want to see any photo.
I've seen Swathi again.
What? Swathi?
- I'll tell you later.
What happened?
-Sharath cut the phone call.
Cut the call?
What's the matter?
It seems he has met Swathi again.
- Met Swathi?
Why are you smiling?
Met Swathi?
Where?
What's the matter?
I want to talk to you.
- I'm waiting.
You wanted to talk but
why are you showing a silent film?
I'll talk.
I've stopped drinking.
You must say something
that will make me happy,
and throw a big party
to every guest in marriage.
You said I mustn't see, talk or smile at you in
marriage, but you've called me here to talk.
I think I've to book a marriage hall
in Mangalore immediately,
Shall I?
What do you think of me?
Did I say I love you?
Why did you tell the photographer
that I'm your lover?
Tell me.
Oh no! Has a comedian turned
villain in my life?
He was irritating me,
so I told him.
What did you tell him?
That I love you.
If there is love in my life, it's you.
- No way!
I never had such feelings for you.
Why should I love a man like you?
Those harsh words you told me
or that slap,
I can never forget that in my life.
Forget about me entering your life.
Please leave me alone without
talking about me to others.
♪ Heart is after an illusion ♪
♪ Heart is after her memories ♪
♪ Eyes are scared to dream ♪
♪ Love appears like distant past ♪
♪ Moon has come down
to go back dirty ♪
♪ Has it risen beautiful
after she left him ♪
♪ I've signed my forehead
with colors ♪
♪ Love is no longer a routine ♪
♪ My shadow has
learned the way ♪
♪ Blind man's dream shows
a horrifying light ♪
♪ Inside the walls of the heart,
the Plumeria flower grows ♪
♪ My smile was gone somewhere
without my knowledge ♪
♪ Inside the walls of the heart,
the Plumeria flower grows ♪
♪ My smile was gone somewhere
without my knowledge ♪
♪ Heart is after an illusion ♪
♪ Heart is after her memories ♪
♪ My boat sunk thus
leaving the sea of eyes ♪
♪ Where is the answer to my question ♪
♪ She is very silent ♪
♪ I desired you from the very beginning ♪
♪ She came back ♪
♪ I know that she was
my anticipated dream ♪
♪ Inside the walls of the heart,
the Plumeria flower grows ♪
♪ My smile was gone somewhere
without my knowledge ♪
♪ Inside the walls of the heart,
the Plumeria flower grows ♪
♪ My smile was gone somewhere
without my knowledge ♪
♪ Heart is after an illusion ♪
♪ Heart is after her memories ♪
Sandeep!
Come here.
Got caught with him again.
I'll hit you with bottle.
I was always 100 meters
away from Sharath.
Come, I've to talk
with you.
Come I say!
What are you doing, Sharath?
Apologizing for my sin.
Forgiveness.
You've become a
bad omen to my life.
I touched you
2 years ago,
I lost my love,
my life and peace.
So, I beg bowing
down at your feet.
Just put your hand on my head
and say you've forgiven me.
Swathi is here only.
She may change her heart
and accept my love.
Why are you thinking?
What's your problem to
say I've forgiven you?
Tell me whatever your problem is,
I'll solve it.
What do you do for living?
I'm still searching
for a job.
Searching for a job?
Will you forgive me
if I get you a job?
One of my close friend
is like God,
I'll send him to you,
ready him a job and
₹ 1 lakh salary,
Is that salary
okay to you?
1...1...
Give him ₹ 1 lakh, okay
At least now say
you've forgiven me.
Say!
Come on say!
Forgiven you.
Did you forgive me?
What's the use?
But she'll not forgive me.
Even if I fall at her feet
wash it with my tears,
she'll not forgive me.
I've become so cheap to her.
The great industrialist Sharath is nothing
but an egoistic brute to her.
Did you fall in love?
No.
Never fall in love.
You're a jockey on falling in love,
you're a good-for-nothing
if love fails.
Like me.
Shall I talk to Swathi?
What will you tell her?
He's a good man,
he got me a job,
his love is true and pure,
accept it.
I came to know a truth today,
if girls decide to forget anyone,
even Lord Brahma, the creator
can't change it.
No, what she did was right.
It wasn't her mistake.
Without knowing what is love
and how to look after lover
I loved her very dearly.
I gave her as much pain too.
Now, I can see her but can't talk,
smile, live or die!
To hell with my damned life!
I'll never get her in my life.
And I can't forget her too.
I can't have her and
I won't forget her.
♪ Shall I forgive him ♪
♪ Lend my hand forgetting the past ♪
♪ My heart is on the way back ♪
♪ Memory is fading ♪
♪ The dream you left has vanished ♪
♪ I'm leaving you so as to
forget the past ♪
♪ Please do forgive me ♪
I can't stay here
for another minute.
Come.
I must go to Bangalore with Sharath.
What are you saying?
I don't know,
I must go with him.
May I?
Friend, I need a help from you.
One of my people want to
go to Bangalore,
you've to drop there.
Okay.
- Call.
Already sitting in your car.
Will you please stop the car
for a while?
I want to talk to you.
Will you please stop the car?
Don't know why I'm worried.
I think you'd go away abroad
on reaching Bangalore.
Please say something, Sharath.
You wanted to talk to me.
That is...
I can't take it anymore.
When you proposed to me
on my birthday,
I told you I'm getting engaged,
it was a lie,
Sharath, that is...
Bastard mustn't escape!
You aspire to become a hero, right?
Show your heroism now!
Bash him, boys!
Leave him!
What happened, madam?
You need to have an MRI scan, sir.
Please come with us, sir.
Specialists are waiting.
I'm fine,
nothing has happened to me.
I'm waiting for her
to regain consciousness.
Just a small test, that's all.
Press and TV media are waiting outside.
Sharath is fine.
Just a little scratch.
Other than that he's perfectly alright.
We're doing just routine tests.
Moreover...
Father...mother...how is Sharath?
Sharath has been taken for a scan.
We haven't met him.
We saw the news on TV.
We came just now.
What happened to you?
Father...
- What will happen to her?
She'll be fine.
Even if we don't have
peace in life, she'll be fine.
Don't talk like that.
I'm saying right.
You entered my son's life once and
we had more pain than happiness.
Are you planning to come back
and ruin peace in our lives?
Won't your words hurt her?
- I'm telling to hurt her.
My son loved her so much.
How much it hurt us!
Have you forgotten it?
Let her also feel that pain.
My son has agreed to marry another girl.
So, I beg you humbly
with folded hands,
please forget him,
please allow us to live in peace,
Sorry, mother.
You wait.
Think of how to correct it.
Father, what mother says is right.
I've already gave you so much of pain.
I mustn't be here.
I'll go away.
Please wait, don't listen to her.
Please father, leave me alone.
If anyone is hurt by me,
I don't like it.
Please leave me.
I beg you.
Sorry, mother.
- Wait...
Scan report is normal.
Father!
- What's this?
What happened?
Nothing has happened to me, dad.
They say whatever happens
it happens for good.
I'll be happy all my life, dad.
I got back my Swathi, dad.
I got back my Swathi.
Haven't you forgotten her yet?
She ruined our peace once, that's enough.
She's not here, she has left.
Where did she go?
- Who knows where?
Please answer him.
Get well soon, I'll tell you everything.
Mother, I'm fine, where's Swathi?.
Wherever she may be who cares,
didn't you promise to marry
the girl of my choice?
What have you done, mom?
When everything was going right...
Where's Swathi, mom?
- I don't know.
Where's Swathi, dad?
Where's Swathi, doctor?
- She left.
Where?
She left crying.
Your matter is going
live coverage since yesterday.
If you come live on TV,
I'm sure you'll find Swathi.
Come.
- Please come.
He's here to talk to you.
Please co-operate.
I'm fine, nothing has happened to me.
Swathi, please listen to me.
It happened by mistake.
Please listen to me,
please come back to me.
I can't live without you, Swathi.
Anyone watching this program,
Swathi's photo...
It's here...here sir.
She's Swathi.
If you find her anywhere,
tell her Sharath loves you dearly.
Please help me to find her.
Please Swathi, I seek your
forgiveness for the mistake.
Please tell everyone.
Where are you Swathi?
Please tell I love her.
Do you've her number?
It's ringing.
Who is it?
This is not Swathi.
This is a stolen phone,
come to Mangalore station and take it.
Railway station?!
Come, let's go.
Go fast...fast...
How far?
- We're very near.
Go Fast...go fast!
Trust me, sir.
You'll get Swathi.
No, you don't know about her.
I made a small mistake and
I had to endure 2 years of pain.
Now a big mistake happened
without my knowledge.
If I miss now,
I'll never get her again.
Never get her.
Everything will be fine, sir.
Give me way...way please...
Sir, lost phone.
Made a phone call, its here only.
You're Sharath, right?
A police officer answered
my phone call.
Is it? Let's go to the office.
Come...come...
Quick...
Please give way!
Please come here.
It seems he got a call about
finding his lost mobile.
Just now I called and
you answered it.
Yes sir, I answered the call.
Where's Swathi? Her mobile.
- Come here.
Tell him.
A girl left by train now,
I stole her bag.
A train left 5 minutes ago.
You can catch it at Sakleshpur
if you go fast.
Come...come...
Industrialist Sharath is desperately
searching for his lady love.
Search there!
Search entire train.
My bag got stolen!
I lost my ticket, mobile
and everything I had.
I came all the way from there with
great difficulty, instead of saying I love you,
are you talking losing ticket and mobile?
I can't live without you.
Won't you say I love you?
I'm not in mood now,
I'll tell after our marriage.
Subtitle done by
Srinath