महोदयाः,
रक्षामन्त्रालयानुसारे त्वयं केवलमभ्यासमेव,
किन्तु गर्वितोऽहं यत् 00-दलमभ्यासे चितम्
लक्ष्यं तु जिब्राल्टारस्य तेजोन्वेषोपलम्भनम् वर्जित्वा प्रवेशम्
SAS-दलमतिसतर्कं भवति तथा भवतऽवरोद्धुमादिष्टम्
किन्तु जानेऽहं यत् भवन्तो ममाशाभङ्गं न कुर्वन्ति.
विजयिनो भवन्तु.
- (कर्गदानि उड्डयन्ते)
- अरे!
धिक्!
हे मित्र! त्वं क्रीडातः बहिः.
क्रीडा समाप्ता. त्वं मृतः
ताम्य!
आआआआ!
(व्याक्रोशः)
हुम्!
तिष्ठ.
अये! तिष्ठ! त्वं मारितः!
अत्र बहुनिरसतामनुभवामि, मार्गौः.
अत्र तु केवलं विलासभोक्तारः टेनिस्-क्रीडकाश्च सन्ति
निजः पुरुषः अपेक्षते!
दूरवागावश्यकी.
सा पुनः दूरभाषं करोति.
- को भवान्?
- बोण्डः! जेम्सबोण्डः
अभ्यासनीयन्त्रण, 007 अस्मि.
होरानन्तरम् निवेत्स्यामि (निवेदनं करोमि)
मया सह कालं यापयति वा?
होरद्वयानन्तरम्.
Hey, driver, where we going?
I swear my nerves are showing
Set my hopes up way too high
The living's in the way we die
Comes the morning
and the headlights fade away
Hundred thousand people
I'm the one they frame
I've been waiting long
For one of us to say
Save the darkness
Let it never fade away
The living daylights
Ah-ah-ah-ah
All right, hold on tight now
It's down, down to the wire
Set your hopes up way too high
The living's in the way we die
Comes the morning
and the headlights fade away
Hundred thousand changes
Ever]/thing's the same
I've been waiting long
For one of us to say
Save the darkness
Let it never fade away
The living daylights
Ah-ah-ah-ah
(Mozart "Symphony No. 40")
सौण्डर्सोऽस्मि वियेन्नाविभागस्य मुख्यः.
अतीव विलम्बः.
इदं कर्तव्यमेव, विलासकारयम् तु न.
वेलास्ति.
- Now, where's our man?
- In the box. Between the KGB minders.
Lovely girl with the cello.
Forget the ladies for once, Bond.
- Koskov will leave here at the interval.
- Sh! Sh!
We'd better go.
Turn off the lights.
Now, let's understand one another, Bond.
General Koskov is a top KGB mastermind.
His defection is my baby. He contacted me.
I've planned this out to the last detail.
- You'll want the soft-nosed ones, I expect.
- No, the steel-tipped.
KGB snipers usually wear body armour.
- What's your escape route?
- Sorry, old man. Section 26, paragraph 5.
That information is on
a need-to-know basis only.
I'm sure you understand.
Koskov is under intensive KGB surveillance.
A sniper has been assigned to watch him
and he expressly asked
for you to protect him.
- Why me?
- He has the impression you're the best.
- Where's the car?
- In the alley out the back.
Bring the chair.
It'll take him about 10 seconds to reach us.
Plenty of time for a sniper
to make strawberry jam of him!
(applause)
There's Koskov now.
What's he waiting for?
Sniper. Two ﬂoors up, centre window.
The girl with the cello!
Fire, Bond, fire!
Shoot her! What are you waiting for?
You missed... Deliberately!
Where is he?
- In the boot.
- First place they'd look.
- But my escape route...
- Scrubbed.
Get in the front.
- James... James Bond!
- Later, General.
Lose them. I'll pick you up at the border.
2300 hours. Be there.
- How will you get him out?
- Sorry, old man.
Section 26, paragraph 5: "need-to-know".
I'm sure you understand.
- The sniper was a woman.
- I noticed.
- Some of the best KGB shots are women.
- Mm-hm.
- Did you...?
- I'd rather not talk about it.
No, of course not.
They are looking for me! If they
close the border, how will I get out?
Don't you worry about that, Georgi.
We have a pipeline to the West.
- Rosika Miklos.
- Our man here.
Good to work with you
again, Mr Bond. Come.
Keep quiet.
(TV sports commentary)
- We must hurry. Get him in the pig.
- Pig? What is pig?
Scouring plug to clean out the pipeline.
This one's been designed to carry a man.
Pipeline? You mean our pipeline?
Great Soviet achievement -
piping natural gas into the West.
- But... Not me!
- Don't worry, Georgi. It's a piece of cake.
Hm! Never mind cake. If you open valve
before 100, he will be borsch!
Pigs! Borsch! Cake!
There must be another way!
Get in. Put on the mask
and breathe normally.
- Enough talk!
- Relax, Georgi.
Our people have spent months on this.
- How many times have you done this?
- You're the first.
Remember... When this says 100,
turn this. Not before.
- Where are you going?
- To take care of the supervisor.
When pig goes, his control panel
will light up like Christmas tree.
(television)
(alarm)
(speaking foreign language)
(rumbling)
(dog barks)
Welcome to Austria, General.
Come on. Up you go.
Come on, hurry up!
(man) That's right. We've got him.
Excuse me. Shut it now.
Thank you.
Cheer up, Saunders.
The operation's a success.
- And officially still yours.
- I don't intend to leave it at that, 007.
I'm telling M you deliberately missed.
Your orders were to kill that sniper.
Stuff my orders. I only kill professionals.
That girl didn't know
one end of a rifle from the other.
Go ahead. Tell M what you want.
If he fires me, I'll thank him for it.
Whoever she was, I must have
scared the living daylights out of her.
(newspaper vendor)
Russian general defects!
Ula Yarkhov. Confirmed kills, three.
Probable kills, two.
Assassination methods:
strangulation with hands or thighs.
James, she's just your type!
Wrong again, Moneypenny. You are.
I'll file that
with the other secret information.
Specialist - child impersonations.
Assassination method:
explosive teddy bears.
That's all the KGB female assassins.
You know, we could try freelancers
stationed outside the Soviet bloc.
It'll have to wait. M wants you
out at the Blayden safe house.
Right. Looks like
it's a dead end here anyway.
- (loud rock music)
- Ah! Good!
Something we're making for
the Americans. It's called a ghetto blaster.
You'd better hurry. M wants you
to stop at Harrods and pick up a parcel.
Moneypenny, ask Records to monitor
Czech publication and news services
for any mention of a woman cellist
at the conservatoire in Bratislava.
I didn't know
you were such a music lover, James.
Any time you want to drop by and
listen to my Barry Manilow collection.
- Sorry, sir. Excuse me.
- Bloody Yanks.
(muffled music)
Good morning, sir.
Control here. 007's on his way.
(music on personal stereo)
(bleeping)
Sorry, Mr Bond.
You'll have to leave the metal.
Thank you, sir.
- Good morning, sir. May I help you?
- No, thanks.
They're in the drawing room.
- (knocks)
- Come.
James!
James, I will never forget
what you did for me!
Thank you so... What's this?
From Harrods. A godsend!
The food here is horrible.
- The foie gras is excellent.
- Da, da. As Russians say,
hearts and stomachs
good comrades make. (laughs)
What's this? Caviar. Well, that's peasant
food for us, but with champagne it's OK.
Bollinger RD. The best! Mm...
The brand on the list was questionable,
sir, so I chose something else.
Superb, Mr Bond!
May I suggest we resume the debriefing?
Absolutely. Go ahead. I'm all yours.
(music on personal stereo)
- Where's the usual milkman?
- What d'you say?
- Where's the usual man?
- Huh... Flu.
- Hey, mate. Watch it!
- Kitchen entrance, round the back.
General Leonid Pushkin is why I defect.
What? Your KGB superior?
Gogol's replacement when
he joined their foreign service.
Once we were like brothers,
but now he's a different man.
Power has gone to his head.
He's sick, like Stalin!
He hates our new policy of détente.
I have here a secret directive
from Pushkin. Smiert Spionom.
- "Death to Spies", Minister.
- Da.
For an assassination programme, with list
of targets - British and American agents.
When this starts, you will retaliate.
Soviet and Western Intelligence
could destroy each other.
This might lead to nuclear war!
Unless Pushkin can be... How do you say?
Put away.
- Where is Pushkin now? In Moscow?
- Da.
But in three days he will leave for Tangier.
Cover - North African trade convention.
Real reason?
New directive.
Minister, in view of the importance
of what Mr Koskov has just told us
I believe we should
consult with higher authority.
- By all means. Good day, Mr Koskov.
- Good day, sir.
There you go. There's a good lad.
- Good morning.
- Morning. Put it down there, would you?
Ta.
Green Four to base!
Green Four, this is control. Where are you?
Green Four?
Argh!
You may have a malfunction
Green Four to base.
We have gas leaks in main building.
Some personnel overcome. Evacuate.
Send for emergency medical services.
Green Four, I read and understand you.
(Tannoy) Control to all stations.
Code 10. Initiate emergency drill.
- (siren)
- Evacuate the main building.
Emergency. Emergency.
All personnel evacuate the main building.
Green Four to base. Major gas explosion.
Keep clear of the main building.
KGB!
Keep back!
- Get up. Come on!
- Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
Move.
Move!
Keep clear of the main building.
Assistance is on its way.
(helicopter)
- Who's that for?
- You, comrade.
Help him or I kill you both.
(Tannoy)
Security must be maintained at all times.
Move! Hurry.
Only emergency sen/ices
should be allowed in the area.
Please be calm
Stay away from the house.
Please don't use your private radiophones
Two dead, two in hospital, and Koskov
probably back in Moscow, if not dead.
We're the laughing stock
of the Intelligence community.
Our first major coup in years, snatched
from right under our noses by the KGB
only hours after he defected!
- No trace of him?
- Nothing.
- Then there's this Pushkin matter.
- Mm. Well, I must be off.
Meeting with the PM this afternoon.
We have to nip Smiert Spionom in the bud.
Pushkin should be in Tangiers
in two days' time.
A termination warrant
has been issued for him.
This plot to kill agents
sounds rather far-fetched, sir.
- I know General Pushkin
- Do you think I don't?
I've dealt with him on several occasions!
Our paths have crossed over the years.
He's tough and resourceful, but...
- I can't believe he's a psychotic.
- Neither did I until today.
This arrived from Gibraltar.
It was found near 004's body.
Your name was on Pushkin's list, too, 007.
There are a few things I'd like to check
out first, sir. That sniper, for instance.
Yes... I've read Saunders' report
You jeopardised the mission
- to avoid shooting a beautiful girl.
- I had to make a split-second decision.
- It was instinct.
- I'll recall 008 from Hong Kong.
He can do it. He doesn't know Pushkin.
He follows orders, not instincts.
- You can take a fortnight's leave.
- No!
Sir.
If it has to be done, I'd rather do it.
Right, bring it down slowly. Gently now.
- Morning, Q.
-Ah, morning, 007. Ow!
Mind your head.
I've got something for you.
We're just winterising this.
Now, pay attention, 007.
- A key-ring finder. (whistles)
- (bleeps)
- Surprise me.
- You arm it by pressing that button there.
Like that. See?
Right. Now wear that.
Right. Now... Whistle
the first bars of "Rule, Britannia
(whistles)
Stun gas. Effective range?
Ooh, about ﬁve feet.
Disorientates any normal person
for about... Ooh, 30 seconds.
You don't find too many
normal people in this business, Q.
What is it to blow up the room -
"God Save the Queen"?
It so happens, 007, that we've packed
the finder with concentrated explosive,
sufficient to remove the door of any safe.
It's magnetic.
The actuating signal is personalised.
- What's my code?
- Oh, most appropriate.
- A wolf whistle.
- You mean, um...
Stop!
You may find the keys useful.
They open 90% of the world's locks.
All right, sit down and
make yourself comfortable.
- Well done, Moneypenny. That's her.
- Records sent over this translation.
"Kara Milovy, talented scholarship cellist,
whose arm was injured
during an intermission last week,
will be at the academy on Thursday,
playing Borodin's
'String Quartet No.2 in D'. "
That's tomorrow.
Moneypenny, I'll need travel documents
for Tangier...via Bratislava.
And keep this between ourselves.
That girl must be very talented.
Believe me, my interest in her
is purely professional.
- Just taking the Aston Martin for a spin
- Be careful, 007.
It's just had a new coat of paint!
(Borodin "String Quartet No.2 in D")
(clinking)
I dropped the gun in the river.
The KGB made quite a mess.
You're English. Who are you?
I heard you play
at the conservatoire yesterday.
It was exquisite.
I saw what happened on the tram.
Where did they take you?
KGB headquarters?
They released me this morning.
Take a look across the street.
They let you go so they could follow you.
I don't understand.
Why are you trying to help me?
What did Pushkin want?
Did he ask you about Georgi Koskov?
He wanted to know where he was.
- Did you tell him?
- No.
That was clever of Georgi...using blanks.
Made the British believe
his defection was real.
How do you know that?
He told me.
- You saw him?
- Two days ago. He's safe and sound.
- You're a friend of his?
- We've been through quite a lot together.
Oh, dear Georgi!
He kept his promise to send for me.
Where are we going? To London?
No, not yet. The British think
he'll be safer if he keeps moving around.
- We might catch up with him in Vienna.
- Vienna?
We must leave immediately,
before they pick you up again.
- But how?
- We'll manage.
Get packed. Bring some warm clothes.
Looks like we got away with it.
My cello! It's at the conservatoire.
- I'll get you another in Vienna.
- No, we must go back for it.
We have 10 minutes before
they discover what's happened.
- I must get my cello.
- No way!
Come on, get in!
Why didn't you learn the violin?
(jazz music on car radio)
(talking on radio)
You've picked up the police band.
There must be an atmospheric anomaly.
They're looking for a foreign car...
A man and a woman.
And a cello!
Looks like they just found us.
(Siren)
Pull over to the side and stop!
- What happened?
- Salt corrosion.
(voices on radio)
They're setting up roadblocks.
- What is this?
- I've had a few optional extras installed.
(machine-gun fire)
Amazing, this modern safety glass.
Look out!
See where this leads to.
This road only leads to the lake.
Time to leave.
- James!
- (siren)
Brace yourself.
We almost made it.
Come on, quick! Go!
(ticking)
Glad I insisted you brought that cello!
Sorry!
Not far now!
Here, wave this.
Duck!
- We've nothing to declare!
- Just a cello!
(call to prayer)
(camera clicks)
(beeping)
If you wait here, sir, I'll find the chief.
General Pushkin, it's a pleasure.
I'm Brad Whitaker.
Didn't expect to see you in Tangiers.
- General Koskov with you?
- Nyet.
War... War has always been
man's main occupation.
Fools say his greatest accomplishments
were the wheel and the alphabet.
I say it's a battering ram and gunpowder.
How do you like my pantheon
of great commanders?
- Butchers.
- Surgeons.
They cutaway society's dead ﬂesh.
Let me show you something.
At ease, Sergeant. This way, sir.
My hobby - the strategy and tactics
of the world's historic battles.
(fanfares and gunﬁre on tape)
Afghanistan, the North-West Frontier, 1895.
The initial trial of the first
automatic machine gun.
The .303-calibre Maxim.
The King's Royal Rifles
wiped out a vastly superior force.
Kept the British in Afghanistan
for another 25 years.
What you Russians need nowadays
is the equivalent of a modern Maxim.
Third-generation starlight scope.
A laser-sighting, short-barrelled
machine pistol. Infantry mini-missiles.
Range - 5km.
And smart... Just fire and forget.
It penetrates all existing armour.
Yes, sir! Samples of everything ordered.
- The order is cancelled.
- Huh?
You'll return our deposit
of $50 million within the next 48 hours.
You can't be serious, General.
Do you know how hard it is
to obtain this equipment?
This is the latest US and European stuff.
I've made commitments,
letters of credit, special payoffs.
We know that you've had our money
in your Swiss account for eight weeks
and that you have made
no payments of any kind.
Look, I can't cancel orders at this late date.
As one soldier to another,
you have my word of honour...
Spare me your military pretensions.
What army did you serve in?
You were expelled
from West Point for cheating.
Then a short stint as
a mercenary in the Belgian Congo.
Later you worked with various criminals
to help finance your first arms deals.
Lies spread by my competitors.
You forget your many
so-called wars of liberation
that I have supplied through General
Koskov. Those are my credentials.
The money in two days, or you'll find
yourself out of business permanently.
Georgi Koskov as well.
I don't know what you two are scheming,
but it is over. ls that understood?
Careful.
Taxi!
Vienna's beautiful, just like Georgi said.
- You care for him a great deal, don't you?
- I owe him everything.
My scholarship
at the conservatoire, my Strad...
- Your cello‘s a Stradivarius?
- A famous one. The Lady Rose.
- Georgi got it in New York.
- Quite a present.
Maybe someday I'll play there.
At Carnegie Hall?
- Georgi believes I can do it.
- I'm sure he's right.
- We go to him now?
- Yeah. Unless he had to move on.
If he did, I'm sure he left a message.
(Viennese waltz)
Danke.
- Careful.
Oh, good afternoon, Mr Bond.
- You will need your usual suite?
- Not tonight, Hans.
- We need a second bedroom.
- Yes, sir.
- Shall I have vodka martinis sent up?
- Shaken, not stirred.
Of course.
Universal Exports.
Bond here. I need two tickets for the
opera tonight, to be left at the box office.
- Do you like it?
- For princess or wife of commissar?
- Let's buy it.
- Don't joke!
- Who will pay?
- Georgi, of course.
Mm... mmm...
Please... Stop it.
The chief wants you.
Oh!
We have to report.
Very good. At ease, Sergeant.
Pushkin wants the money back.
Don't worry. We've convinced
the British that Pushkin is a danger.
They will send their best man,
James Bond, to eliminate him.
I'm not convinced. Necros can do it.
I've worked with the Russians.
My appearance is well known to them.
It could jeopardise my comrades
who depend upon me.
And they depend upon me. Where else
will they find a supply of arms?
Our basic plan is sound.
Pushkin is... How you say... History.
Not yet. James Bond
hasn't laid a finger on him.
- The British are cautious.
- Yeah.
An additional inducement will ensure this.
For instance,
if another agent were... Eliminated...
Do it. But if Pushkin is alive on
the last day of the conference, kill him!
(Mozart "The Marriage of Figaro")
- All my life I've dreamed of this.
- You might play here one day.
That's too much to hope for.
Excuse me for a few moments.
- ls that...?
- The cello girl.
- The KGB sniper? Why bring her here?
- She's not a KGB sniper.
She's Koskov's girlfriend.
She shot blanks to make
his defection look real to us.
Koskov's defection phoney?
The KGB snatched him back.
That's what we were supposed to think.
These are serious accusations, Bond.
What are you up to?
I'm posing as Koskov's friend
to see what leads I can get from her.
You know he bought her a cello
in New York called the Lady Rose?
- A cello with a name?
- Mm-hm. It's a Stradivarius.
They all have names.
Where would Koskov get the money?
Check it out.
I'll need papers for her... Tonight. I have
to get her out of the country by tomorrow.
Here. I took these this afternoon.
Look, this is highly irregular.
I won't get the OK from London today.
It can't wait, Saunders. That girl's
our only chance of getting Koskov back.
(bell rings)
Very well.
I've got nothing to lose but my pension.
Meet me at the Prater Cafe
near the Ferris wheel at midnight.
- No more.
- This one!
Waaaargh! Ha ha ha ha ha!
Take me on the wheel.
You'll be able to see better.
(music on personal stereo)
- Bal/on, mein Herr?
- Nein.
Is it real or just a dream?
What's wrong? Why do we stop?
I arranged it.
We could be here all night.
Don't.
It's impossible.
Knowing you only two days and all I can
think of is how we would be together.
Don't think.
Just let it happen.
(laughter)
Do you want another ride?
I'll be back in a minute.
There may be a message for me.
(personal stereo)
Where has every body gone?
(bleeps)
It was bought recently
at auction in New York.
Lot 124, the Lady Rose,
a cello by Stradivarius of Cremona, 1724.
SO|d for $150,000
to Brad Whitaker.
Whitaker? The arms dealer?
The same.
Koskov and Whitaker...
- Where's Whitaker now?
- At his place in Tangier.
Well done.
Good luck.
Saunders...
Thanks.
Where are you going?
What's the matter?
Bad accident back there.
Did you hear?
Hear from Georgi?
Yes.
I got the message.
He's with Whitaker in Tangier.
Brad Whitaker? The American?
- You know him?
- He's a patron of the arts.
Georgi said he'd help me.
How soon do we have to go?
Immediately. I promised Georgi
I'd get you back as soon as I could.
Can't we stay here a few days?
No. We leave first thing in the morning.
(Moroccan music)
ls anything wrong?
- Bond!
- Don't make any sudden moves, General.
Go to the table.
Sit down.
I take it that this is not a social call, O07.
Correct. You should have brought lilies.
- May I ask why?
- Smien‘ Spionom.
Smiert Spionom?
That was a Beria operation in Stalin's
time. It was deactivated 20 years ago.
- Two of our agents are dead.
- My condolences.
We had nothing to do with it.
Where's Koskov?
He disappeared two weeks ago.
I was about to have him arrested.
- Why?
- For misusing state funds.
Involving Whitaker?
That is a security matter
and cannot be discussed.
(beeping)
That was damn stupid!
Get in the bathroom and lock the door.
Stay where you are!
Get down on your knees.
Put your hands behind your back.
You are professional.
You do not kill without reason.
Two of our men are dead.
Koskov's named you.
- Now, why should I disobey my orders?
- I am in the dark as much as you are.
It is a question of trust. Who do you believe?
Koskov... Or me?
If I trusted Koskov, we wouldn't be talking.
But as long as you're alive,
we'll never know what he's up to.
Then I must die.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my honour to introduce
the head of the Russian delegation,
Comrade Leonid Pushkin.
Comrade delegates,
I bring you profound fraternal greetings
from your comrades in Soviet Union.
(gunshots)
No! No!
Seal the building!
(speaks Arabic)
(woman sobs)
Hey! You looking for a party?
Seems like a good idea.
I'm sorry to put you through that, my dear.
It is the first time I've ever been grateful
that James Bond is a good shot!
Pull over here. We can have a party
some other time. A little present for you.
Not enough? Take it all.
Just sit back and enjoy the ride.
Down below.
What the hell are you trying to do, 007?
Start World War Ill?
Felix Leiter!
Now, what's the CIA doing here?
Nice work, girls.
- No hard feelings?
- Not if the party's still on.
It's a long story, Felix, but in the end
Pushkin makes a miraculous recovery.
You mean this is a put-up job?
- What's all this?
- We've been watching Pushkin
since he met two days ago with Whitaker.
- An illegal arms deal with the Russians?
- You've got me, James.
Whitaker has a few samples of hi-tech
stuff, but he's placed no big orders yet.
Looks like we're working on the same
case from opposite ends. Let's talk shop.
Ah! Well done!
Congratulations. We heard it over the radio.
I didn't kill him. Bond did.
- I told you the British believed me!
- (phone rings)
I told you!
Now we can move. I'll signal
Amsterdam to ship the diamonds.
- Sir?
- Hello? Yes.
Who?
It's for you.
Hello?
(cello music)
Where have you been, James?
You were gone so long, I was worried!
It's always nice to be missed.
Still no sign of Georgi.
- No, please. Go on playing.
- No.
Let's have a drink.
You remembered.
To us.
Na zdra vi ye
Did I get it right?
Mmm... Perfect.
What's the matter?
Kara, it's time I told you the truth.
I'm not a friend of Georgi's.
I'm a British agent looking for him.
He's betrayed us all, Kara.
The Russians, the British,
even you.
He told us a sniper might try to kill him.
And he set you up as the sniper, Kara.
He wants you dead. You knew too much.
Liar! You pretended to love me!
I telephoned Whitaker.
Georgi was there. He told me the truth.
You're a KGB agent,
using me to find him and kill him!
No, that's not...
That's not true. I...
That's. ..
Chloral hydrate!
- Keep your hands off me!
- Kara, listen to me!
The riﬂe was shot out of your hands.
- How do you know?
- Because I was the...
I was the man sent to kill you.
Why didn't you?
Kara, my darling,
you were absolutely perfect.
L-luFFY
(Siren)
Sortez, s'iI vous plait.
Merci, monsieur.
Open it, please.
Careful. It must be kept absolutely sterile.
Urgh! Go.
I've been such a fool.
We both have.
Open the lid.
(93393) Oh, my God!
That's not human. It's an animal's heart.
Diamonds hidden in the ice.
(toilet ﬂushes)
- How can I help you?
- I need my key ring. Look out!
(Bond groans)
Black coffee for our guest.
She has so many talents!
I'm curious.
- Why didn't you kill me?
- Oh, I'm not a barbarian, James.
I'm taking you
to the proper Soviet authorities
for the killing of General Pushkin.
You're a wonder, Georgi!
You get me to kill Pushkin for you.
Then you turn me in
to the Russians for his murder.
What are you going to ask for? Immunity?
Permission to emigrate
and enjoy the amenities of the West?
You don't think they'll
condone your defection?
What defection?
I have been on a secret mission
for General Pushkin
to disinform British Intelligence.
I'm sorry, James.
For you I have great affection,
but we have an old saying:
"Duty has no sweethearts."
We have an old saying, too, Georgi.
And you're full of it!
Come, Kara.
- Kara?
- Yes.
Welcome to Afghanistan.
Colonel Feyador, my old comrade in arms.
I have here General Pushkin's assassin.
British Agent O07, James Bond.
See he is sent to Moscow.
One moment. There's one more.
Take her, too. She's a defector.
I will be compassionate with you
and try to have you assigned to
the Siberian Philharmonic Orchestra.
They're quite good
despite their bourgeois repertoire.
I am on a secret state mission. I need
a detachment of men and some trucks.
- Ah! What are these here for?
- For murder.
Murder? Ah!
I haven't had a woman prisoner
for a long time!
(laughter)
Come.
Russky! Has Colonel Feyador
considered my appeal?
Yes. Good news.
You won't be hung in the morning.
You will be shot!
It's all a mistake! I stole nothing!
You can tell Allah when you see him!
- Strip!
- Nye smeyete menya trogat!
Shout all you want. It's soundproofed.
They don't like to hear screaming at night.
I didn't tell you to get down!
I did not tell you to get up!
Now... Get up!
- (whistles)
- (key ring beeps)
(whistles "Rule, Britannia")
James!
(prisoner laughs)
Lock the door.
You were fantastic! We're free!
Kara, we're in a Russian air base in the
middle of Afghanistan. Try the small key.
At least we're together.
Terrific. Come on.
Please.
Ha ha ha ha!
(shouts in Russian)
(sirens)
Come on, jump!
(shouts in Afghan)
- What's going on?
- I tell them you no Russian.
- They no kill you now.
- How about later?
Don't worry. They'll save you for the harem!
It's the work of the mujaheddin.
Mujaheddin?
The Afghan Resistance.
(shouting)
(speaks in Afghan)
(shouts in Afghan)
I hope he's not invited to dinner.
(English accent) Thank you both
for your help. My name is Kamran Shah.
Please forgive the theatricals.
It's a hangover from my Oxford days.
I'm sure you'd like to freshen up.
It's all right, go ahead.
- I have to get back to the air base.
- (laughs) You must be crazy!
- Half the Russian army's looking for you!
- You won't help?
No.
Then put me in touch with the mujaheddin.
(laughter)
Deputy Commander of the Eastern District.
I was caught reconnoitring the air base.
Thankfully they didn't know who I was.
Now, who are you?
- I work for the British government.
- (laughter)
We've uncovered a plot by General Koskov
to purchase American hi-tech weapons.
Arms that could be used
against you and your men.
That is important. You must go to
our commander in the Khyber Pass.
That could take days. I have to get back
to the air base before Koskov leaves.
Look, come with us tomorrow.
After our mission, I'll see what I can do.
That'll be too late.
- I need a gun and some guides.
- Impossible.
I cannot spare men or the horses.
And now it is time to rest.
We leave at sunrise.
I was worried for you, James.
What's going to happen to us?
Kheista.
What does that mean?
It means beautiful...in Afghan.
We're with the mujaheddin.
We leave with them in the morning
on some kind of operation.
And you're going to the Khyber Pass.
You're not coming with me?
No. I'll catch up with you later.
You're going back for Georgi, aren't you?
- It's too dangerous. Don't go.
- I have to.
You have to what? Get killed?
- I won't wait for you.
- Fine.
Then I'll have Kamran
send you direct to London.
You dumb, stubborn, stupid...
Konska zadnice!
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Back end of horse!
Are you calling me a horse's arse?
I might never see you again.
You will.
I promise.
(shouting in Afghan)
Raw opium. Worth half a billion
dollars on the streets of New York.
(Qunfi re)
- What are you up to? Selling dope?
- Not so loud.
- That's the chief of the Snow Leopards.
- Who?
- The biggest opium dealer in the area.
- I've worked for them.
I don't care if the Russians die
from my bullets or their opium!
Besides, we need the money to buy arms.
- Georgi!
- And the diamonds.
He arranged for the Russians
to buy many hi-tech weapons.
He's using the down payment
to buy this opium instead.
He can turn a huge profit in days and
still provide the Russians with their arms.
- Unless...
- Go on.
If the opium never arrives...
The Snow Leopard Brotherhood
are dangerous to cross.
This is their biggest deal since the invasion.
You won't help?
(shouts in Afghan)
Perhaps. As long as nothing is done
till the Russians pay up and leave.
Right. I'll need
some plastic explosives and a timer.
I'll see what I can do.
(speaks in Afghan)
(Necros shouts in Afghan)
James is trapped. You must help him!
- He'll have to take his chances.
- You owe him your life!
- There's nothing more I can do.
- Yes, there is!
- Women!
- (cheering)
(horse whinnies)
Wait here. We'll come back for you.
(shouts in Russian)
Bond!
Don't shoot! Don't destroy the plane.
(shouts in Russian)
- Block the runway!
- Da.
(shouts in Russian)
The tanker!
James!
(engine doesn't start)
Where is she?
We have to stop him!
Kara!
James!
(Qunfi re)
Don't shoot! You'll hit the plane!
- Kara!
- Oh, my God!
Jump!
Now that you're here, take over.
- What?
- Hold this and keep it straight and level.
- Where are you going?
- To defuse a bomb.
No!
Please!
(bomb ticking)
- What happened?
- He got the boot.
(screams)
(shouts in Afghan)
Take over. Hold it steady.
- Where are you going?
- To drop a bomb.
(beeping)
What's the matter?
We're losing fuel fast!
I just hope we can make Pakistan.
There's no place to put down.
(buzzer sounds)
Go in the back. Get in the Jeep. Quickly!
Fasten your seat belt!
Hold on!
I know a great restaurant in Karachi.
We can just make dinner!
(call to prayer)
Whitaker's on the ground ﬂoor.
Koskov is in an upstairs bedroom.
Guard in the pool area near you.
Guard clear. Proceed.
Hold it.
He's coming back.
Go, James. Over and out.
Well, he's in.
(explosions)
Pickett's charge was up
Cemetery Ridge, not Little Round Top.
I'm replaying the battle
as I would have fought it.
Meade was tenacious but he was cautious.
He missed his chances
to crush Lee at Gettysburg.
I've come for Koskov.
Well, hell, you can have him!
Soon as I get my opium.
- Now where is it?
- Up in smoke.
- You burned up a half a billion bucks?
- Mm-hm.
That's too bad, Bond.
You know, you could have been a live,
rich man instead of a poor, dead one.
You're finished, Whitaker. If the Russians
don't get you, the Americans will.
Nah.
You know, Meade should have
taken another 35,000 casualties.
He could have ended
the rebellion right then.
Hell, Grant would have done it.
Right, you've had your eight.
Now I'll have my 80!
Sorry to say your popgun is no match
for the latest body armour!
(remote control beeps)
Should have known you'd take refuge
behind that British vulture Wellington!
You know he had to buy German
mercenaries to beat Napoleon, don't you?
(wolf-whistles)
I owed you that one, Bond.
He met his Waterloo.
General Pushkin!
Thank God you're still alive!
Whitaker has held me here for weeks.
Thank you for rescuing me! Thank you!
Georgi! Georgi!
- Put him on the next plane to Moscow.
- Oh, thank you, General!
Thank you so much! Thank you!
In the diplomatic bag.
What about Kara?
She is a defector, too.
What shall we do about her?
(Dvorék "Cello Concerto ")
Are you going to stay in France now?
Oh, you were marvellous!
Will you excuse us?
General Gogol, Miss Kara Milovy.
Magnificent! I hope you can find time
to play in Moscow very soon.
It's all right. General Gogol
is with their foreign service.
He's arranged an immigration visa,
so you can come and go as you like.
Wonderful!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry we missed the concert.
We had some trouble at the airport.
I can't imagine why! General Gogol,
I don't believe you've met Kamran Shah.
- My pleasure.
- Where's James?
- Unhappily, he's on assignment abroad.
- I'll be with you shortly.
- (whistles)
- (key ring beeps)
- (Bond whistles)
- (whistles)
- (key ring beeps)
You didn't think I'd miss
this performance, did you?
Oh, James.
If there was a man I could dream of
I'd dream about a dream come true
If there was a man I could ever love
I'd wait a million years
For someone just like you
All my life I've been belated
Never taken any chances
Always hesitated
Where's the prayer?
Where's the glory?
Where's the one I'm holding out for?
When's he walking through the door
The one that you walked through
If he isn't you?
If there was a man I could dream of
I'd dream about a dream come true
If there was a man I could ever love
I'd wait a million years
For someone just like you
Happy endings
Never ﬁnd me
I've put all my fantasies
And hopes of love behind me
Saw my moments over, doomed, but
If there was a man out there for me
I wish it would be
someone who could love me too
If someone was you
English - US - SDH